但我并没有等着其他人出现，我们需要启动这项法案51
but I was not waiting for anybody else to show up we need to start this bill 51
to show up we need to start this bill 51 so I'm gonna try to finish state-space
所以今天我要尝试完成状态空间模型
so I'm gonna try to finish state-space models today there will be more things
models today there will be more things in where they are then unbelievers as
然后他们像他们所说的那样是不信的，而且还可以，所以我在哪里
in where they are then unbelievers as they say and more okay so where I was
they say and more okay so where I was gonna say what we are trying to finish
要说些什么，我们要根据这些来完成状态，但是有很多
gonna say what we are trying to finish states based on those but there is lots
states based on those but there is lots of stuff in the notes that I don't think
我认为我不会涵盖的笔记中的内容，这样您就不会得到
of stuff in the notes that I don't think I will cover so that you don't get a
I will cover so that you don't get a headache and also we can discuss more
头痛，我们也可以讨论更多的话题，所以我今天想做的是
headache and also we can discuss more topics so what I want to do today is
topics so what I want to do today is something sort of elementary and some
我们拥有的事物中蕴含的某种基本和某些方式
something sort of elementary and some ways implied in in the things we have
ways implied in in the things we have seen before I you know so last lecture
在我知道之前见过，所以上一讲我们衍生了历史问题的转折点
seen before I you know so last lecture we derived the turn of history questions
we derived the turn of history questions for linear dynamical systems from
对于从头开始的线性动力系统，基本上我们看了
for linear dynamical systems from scratch basically we looked at the
scratch basically we looked at the questions we said this this independence
问题，我们说这种独立的关系和概率玩
questions we said this this independence relations and playing with probability
relations and playing with probability laws we derived the the color pintura
定律，我们推导出了颜色pintura问题，所以我想做的就是
laws we derived the the color pintura question so what I want to do is I want
question so what I want to do is I want to show you that in essence everything
告诉你，实质上，当我们
to show you that in essence everything we learn about rest is passing when we
we learn about rest is passing when we apply that to the other amical systems
将其应用于其他amical系统实际上将直接给我们
apply that to the other amical systems actually will give us directly the the
actually will give us directly the the the color of military questions and can
军事问题的颜色，也可以一概而论，所以我要
the color of military questions and can be generalized as well so I'm going to
be generalized as well so I'm going to do this highlight basically some of the
这样做基本上突出了他们走的方式的某些推导，但事实并非如此
do this highlight basically some of the derivation the way they go they are not
derivation the way they go they are not trivial so so in some sense you're doing
琐碎的，所以从某种意义上说，您正在使用主人通过的额外机场，但是
trivial so so in some sense you're doing extra airport using masters passing but
extra airport using masters passing but at the expense basically of having an
基本上以拥有这种非常普遍的算法为代价
at the expense basically of having an algorithm of this very general okay in
algorithm of this very general okay in considering the district or some
考虑地区或一些概率图形模型，我们
considering the district or some probabilistic graphical models what we
probabilistic graphical models what we have to do I will suggest actually that
必须要做的，实际上我建议你们
have to do I will suggest actually that you guys'
you guys' the homework 5 maybe you do some of the
作业5也许您做了一些分析计算，
the homework 5 maybe you do some of the analytical calculations that we
analytical calculations that we discussed today because there is much to
今天讨论的是因为有很多东西要学，而且不是很困难
discussed today because there is much to learn and they are not very difficult
learn and they are not very difficult but in essence if you do them you have a
但从本质上讲，如果您这样做，您对两位大师的传承都有很好的感觉，但是
but in essence if you do them you have a good sense of both masters passing but
good sense of both masters passing but also of you know dealing with the carbon
你们也知道在两种类型的方程中处理碳的问题
also of you know dealing with the carbon of in two types of equations all right
of in two types of equations all right so let me review for you the factor
因此，让我为您回顾与状态相对应的因子图
so let me review for you the factor graph that corresponds to the state
graph that corresponds to the state space model of interest the only thing
唯一感兴趣的空间模型是我想要的
space model of interest the only thing that is different here that I want to
that is different here that I want to remind you is that the way that we
提醒您，我们定义结构节点的方式是
remind you is that the way that we define the structure nodes we
define the structure nodes we incorporated both the transition model P
结合了Z值从Zn减去1到N的Z转变模型P
incorporated both the transition model P of Z enthusiam from Zn minus 1 to the N
of Z enthusiam from Zn minus 1 to the N but also the observation model so keep
而且还有观察模型，因此请记住这一点，因此看起来就像
but also the observation model so keep that in mind so it looks like a same
that in mind so it looks like a same thing but in reality we have accounted
事物，但实际上我们已经考虑了
thing but in reality we have accounted for what probability non-factor in
for what probability non-factor in similarly for the first part of her age
同样，在她的年龄的第一部分，是初始状态的概率
similarly for the first part of her age is the probability of the initial state
is the probability of the initial state in the observation model in the initial
在初始状态的观察模型中
in the observation model in the initial State
State alright so the message passing and you
好的，这样消息就可以通过了，您不必记住任何问题
alright so the message passing and you don't have to remember any questions
don't have to remember any questions because really it is graphical so let's
因为实际上它是图形的，所以让我们专注于这个方程式
because really it is graphical so let's concentrate on this equation we only
concentrate on this equation we only look at messages that factors past the
看一下鼻子右边实际上可以做的超过节点的因素的消息
look at messages that factors past the node all right the nose can actually do
node all right the nose can actually do anything in this draft so the message
该草案中的任何内容，因此从FN到Zn的信息本身就是所有因素
anything in this draft so the message from FN to Zn is the factor itself all
from FN to Zn is the factor itself all right which connects the bottom of Zn
连接Zn减1的底部的右边是G n乘以以下信息：
right which connects the bottom of Zn minus 1 is G n times the message that
minus 1 is G n times the message that the factor of Zn minus 1 that is some
Zn负1的因子（即一些弯曲的空气）通过时会注意到N负1
the factor of Zn minus 1 that is some curved air passes to note the N minus 1
curved air passes to note the N minus 1 well it makes sense whatever comes st.
好吧，无论发生什么事情都有意义。再加上因子，那么您就可以将N积分
well it makes sense whatever comes st. plus the factor then you integrate the N
plus the factor then you integrate the N minus 1 out and you get the earth now if
减去1，如果变量连续，您将得到地球。
minus 1 out and you get the earth now if this the variables are continuous would
this the variables are continuous would be in our problem
在我们的问题中，求和将是必不可少的
be in our problem that summation would be an integral okay
that summation would be an integral okay the first equation basically says that
第一个等式基本上是说音符为正的信息
the first equation basically says that the message that the notes positive
the message that the notes positive factor is the same as the message the
因数与已知来自总线的消息相同，因此
factor is the same as the message the previous from the bus is known so in
previous from the bus is known so in essence it emphasizes that we are just
本质上，它强调我们只为处理消息而感到高兴
essence it emphasizes that we are just happy enough to only work with messages
happy enough to only work with messages from factors to know you don't need to
从各种因素中得知您不必为多方交易而烦恼
from factors to know you don't need to bother progressing for multiparty all
bother progressing for multiparty all right so this is the common message
对，所以这是传递的常见消息，我们称其为Alpha
right so this is the common message passing and we call this the alpha
passing and we call this the alpha message okay and we discuss sort of two
信息还可以，我们讨论了两种不同的符号，您知道一个
message okay and we discuss sort of two different notations you know one that
different notations you know one that the message corresponding to this it was
给定所有数据，对应于此的消息是Zn的后验
the message corresponding to this it was the posterior of Zn given all the data
the posterior of Zn given all the data at the time and and I think another
当时，我认为另一种表示法是尼姑标准化后路
at the time and and I think another notation was a nun normalized posterior
notation was a nun normalized posterior effectively so if you don't want to get
有效地，所以如果您不想与该表示法混淆
effectively so if you don't want to get confused with the notation effectively
confused with the notation effectively you can write that this is proportional
您可以说这与您在右侧看到的成正比
you can write that this is proportional to what you see on the right-hand side
to what you see on the right-hand side so when you compute the right-hand side
因此，当您计算右侧时，可以对其进行归一化，
so when you compute the right-hand side then you normalize it and you get a
then you normalize it and you get a distribution so one way or another
分布，所以如果您看到一种或另一种形式，这并不重要
distribution so one way or another it doesn't really matter if you see
it doesn't really matter if you see different notations okay so this is the
可以使用不同的符号，所以这是转发消息，我也想展示一下
different notations okay so this is the forward messages and I also want to show
forward messages and I also want to show you the same schematic basically the
您相同的示意图基本上是从根到无的反向消息
you the same schematic basically the backward messages from the root to no
backward messages from the root to no dates to the left so the message the
日期在左侧，因此消息传递的消息基本上是相同的
dates to the left so the message the message passing is basically identical
message passing is basically identical to before the things but it goes
到事物之前，但它向后退，因此来自
to before the things but it goes backwards so the message from the
backwards so the message from the factory and the little the masters from
工厂和来自n加一的小大师们注意结束
factory and the little the masters from at n plus one to note the end alright so
at n plus one to note the end alright so again we are making a messages from
再次，我们从实践到笔记都做了一条信息，所以这里的信息
again we are making a messages from practice to notes so this message here
practice to notes so this message here okay
好的，这是因素吗
okay is this factor
is this factor why is the message without the factor of
为什么该消息没有十加二美分的因素才能记下ZL加一
why is the message without the factor of ten plus two cents to note ZL plus one
ten plus two cents to note ZL plus one which is this and obviously this message
就是这个，显然这个消息和那个业务是一样的，所以再说一次
which is this and obviously this message the same as that business right so again
the same as that business right so again this message is this factor times this
这个消息是这个因子乘以这个消息，我们整合到n
this message is this factor times this message where we integrate out to the n
message where we integrate out to the n plus one and obviously you can see that
再加上一个，显然您会看到这个过程是倒退的，因为我们
plus one and obviously you can see that this process is backwards because we
this process is backwards because we require this message to the right to
要求此消息在右边以计算其余部分在左边
require this message to the right to compute the rest to the left and the
compute the rest to the left and the integration is to the variables to the
积分在右边的变量中，在这种情况下为Zn加1
integration is to the variables to the right which is in this case Zn plus 1
right which is in this case Zn plus 1 and we call this the mega message okay
我们称其为“大消息”，所以较大的消息向后退
and we call this the mega message okay so the bigger message go backwards the
so the bigger message go backwards the Alpha message is to go forward so what
Alpha消息是要继续前进，所以我要去做的就是
Alpha message is to go forward so what I'm gonna do is I'm going to play with
I'm gonna do is I'm going to play with its equations and device for you they
它的方程式和设备为您，他们提出了三个问题，它看起来
its equations and device for you they come up in three questions and it looks
come up in three questions and it looks sort of a massive algebraic calculation
大量的代数计算，但我建议您这样做，因为
sort of a massive algebraic calculation but I recommend that you do it because
but I recommend that you do it because not only you'll be happy that you
您不仅会发现卡尔曼滤波器方程式而感到高兴
not only you'll be happy that you discover the Kalman filter equations
discover the Kalman filter equations from a completely different way from the
与完全不同于碳驱动器的方式完全不同
from a completely different way from the way carbon driver which is actually
way carbon driver which is actually different from the one we already have
与我们在先前的讲座中已经做过的有所不同，但是有
different from the one we already have done in the earlier lecture but there is
done in the earlier lecture but there is much to learn both from Esther's passing
从以斯帖的过世和与高斯人的比赛中可以学到很多东西
much to learn both from Esther's passing and playing with a gaussians
and playing with a gaussians conditionals partial answers to things
有条件地部分回答类似的问题，所以我将使用
conditionals partial answers to things like that okay so I am going to use
like that okay so I am going to use first the form of the question that
首先是定义Alpha消息的问题形式
first the form of the question that defines the Alpha messages so and again
defines the Alpha messages so and again as I told you if you don't you know want
就像我告诉你的，如果你不知道，你会担心标准化常数是什么
as I told you if you don't you know want to worry what the normalization constant
to worry what the normalization constant here is or without fires you don't need
这是有火还是没有火，您不必费心，好吧，您只需说这是
here is or without fires you don't need to bother okay you just say this is
to bother okay you just say this is proportional throughout and you
在整个过程中都成比例，您会正常化，并祝您好运
proportional throughout and you normalize and with every good luck to be
normalize and with every good luck to be the Alpha messages but fear I'm writing
Alpha消息，但担心我会以精确的方式编写它，
the Alpha messages but fear I'm writing it in a precise for okay where this
it in a precise for okay where this message is the posterior of Zn given
给定所有观测日期，消息是Zn的后验。
message is the posterior of Zn given all the the date of the observations of
all the the date of the observations of Japan man okay
日本男人好，这个报价是GL Scylla是
Japan man okay and this quotation is GL Scylla is
and this quotation is GL Scylla is basically the probability of friction
基本上再给定X 1至X n减1的摩擦概率
basically the probability of friction given X 1 to X n minus 1 okay again
given X 1 to X n minus 1 okay again if you like this rather than having this
如果您喜欢这个，而不是拥有这种过滤分布，那么我们可以联合
if you like this rather than having this filtering distribution we have the joint
filtering distribution we have the joint distribution of Zn relaxed one to excel
锌的分布放松了一个卓越的表现，您将无法获得TN的功能，但
distribution of Zn relaxed one to excel you're not going to get that TN okay but
you're not going to get that TN okay but more or less the question of sort of the
或多或少都存在同样的问题，所以如果您看这些
more or less the question of sort of the same alright so if you look at these
same alright so if you look at these equations right and obviously we're
方程是正确的，显然我们要进行求和和积分
equations right and obviously we're gonna make that summation and integral
gonna make that summation and integral and we want to get a methodology to make
我们想得到一种方法来推导一个推理算法，即
and we want to get a methodology to make derive an inference algorithm that is
derive an inference algorithm that is linearly the length of the chain
线性地我们需要利用链条的长度
linearly the length of the chain we need sort of to take advantage of the
we need sort of to take advantage of the structure of this equation in a way that
等式的结构，当我们在这里插入任何东西时
structure of this equation in a way that when we plug in here whatever
when we plug in here whatever distribution this alpha lessons is we
分发此Alpha课是，我们希望获得相同的
distribution this alpha lessons is we would like to get the same sort of
would like to get the same sort of distribution for the masses out partying
群众集会，从某种意义上说，这属于
distribution for the masses out partying and in some sense if this belongs to
and in some sense if this belongs to some family of distributions we would
一些发行版系列，我们希望在以下情况下唯一要做的事情
some family of distributions we would like the only thing to have to do when
like the only thing to have to do when we apply this equation to update the
我们应用此方程式更新此分布的参数以获得
we apply this equation to update the parameters of this distribution to get
parameters of this distribution to get the distribution of GA right so this is
GA权利的分配，所以这是一个高斯，例如，它将是
the distribution of GA right so this is a Gaussian for example right it would be
a Gaussian for example right it would be great if somehow this is also a Gaussian
如果这也是某种高斯的话，那太好了，我们要做的唯一一件事就是
great if somehow this is also a Gaussian and the only thing we have to do is
and the only thing we have to do is update the mean and the variance of the
更新以前的分布的均值和方差，现在这是
update the mean and the variance of the previous distribution okay now this was
previous distribution okay now this was doing gaussians right and this you know
正确地进行高斯运算，您知道这将完全适合任何分布
doing gaussians right and this you know will fit perfectly with any distribution
will fit perfectly with any distribution from the exponential family but today we
来自指数族，但今天我们将基本上讨论高斯
from the exponential family but today we will discuss basically this the Gaussian
will discuss basically this the Gaussian distribution okay
分布还可以
现在，如果是这样，我们将在状态空间模型中再选一位兰德小姐，
will discuss basically this the Gaussian distribution okay
now if so we're gonna take another Miss Landow in state space model where
现在，如果是这样，我们将在状态空间模型中再选一位兰德小姐，
Landow in state space model where basically what the probability of Zn
从根本上说，锌给CN造成创伤的概率和
basically what the probability of Zn given CN - trauma and the probability of
given CN - trauma and the probability of Excel given Zn are Gaussian and then at
给定Zn的Excel是高斯，然后在一天结束时基本上所有
Excel given Zn are Gaussian and then at the end of the day basically all the
the end of the day basically all the distributions were going to get will be
将会得到的分布将是高斯分布，因此
distributions were going to get will be gaussians so the Joint Distribution of
gaussians so the Joint Distribution of correlated volumes to be a multivariate
相关的体积是多元高斯，我们实际上已经看到了
correlated volumes to be a multivariate Gaussian and we have seen actually this
Gaussian and we have seen actually this problem letting you have done it you
让您做完的问题，您就完成了一项家庭作业问题
problem letting you have done it you sort of done a homework problem with
sort of done a homework problem with this but we will see a different
这个，但是我们在这里会看到不同的观点，所以让我给你
this but we will see a different perspective here so let me give you the
perspective here so let me give you the result summary of the results if you
结果的结果摘要（如果您申请高斯线性系统）
result summary of the results if you apply for a Gaussian linear system the
apply for a Gaussian linear system the forward fasting message equations did
前向禁食消息方程式是否得到了相同的方程式
forward fasting message equations did you get the identical equations
you get the identical equations corresponding to the color filter okay
对应滤色镜好吗，如果您套用支持三个问题
corresponding to the color filter okay if you apply the support three questions
if you apply the support three questions so you know this is the bigger message
所以你知道这是更大的信息，你会得到评论电机方程
so you know this is the bigger message you get the comments motor equations
you get the comments motor equations that I think if I remember we didn't
我想，如果我记得我们没有时间在上一堂课上讲，我可能会
that I think if I remember we didn't have time to cover in last lecture I may
have time to cover in last lecture I may be wrong but you stop there but you can
是错误的，但您到此为止，但您可以想象，类似于beta消息
be wrong but you stop there but you can imagine that similar to the beta message
imagine that similar to the beta message right this government's motion equations
对，这个政府的运动方程基本上会给我们后验
right this government's motion equations basically will give us the posterior of
basically will give us the posterior of specific variables given all the data
给定所有从1到大写字母T的所有数据的特定变量，这就是为什么
specific variables given all the data from 1 to capital T okay that's why this
from 1 to capital T okay that's why this equations are quote is moving a
方程是引用正在移动一个问题，所以这是很好的权利
equations are quote is moving a questions so this is nice right
questions so this is nice right phone that gives me the Kalman filter
能让我看到卡尔曼滤波器条的移动方程式的手机
phone that gives me the Kalman filter bar forgives with it's moving equations
bar forgives with it's moving equations and actually if you do the forward on
实际上，如果您在问题的后面继续前进，则可以得到
and actually if you do the forward on the back of the questions you can get
the back of the questions you can get the sufficient statistics from the
来自隐藏变量的足够统计信息
the sufficient statistics from the hidden variables that are needed to
hidden variables that are needed to compute the parameters view expectation
计算参数视图期望最大化，您知道，当我们
compute the parameters view expectation maximization you know ever that when we
maximization you know ever that when we did the hmm so we will actually turn to
嗯，所以我们实际上将为您转向我们的水晶亮点
did the hmm so we will actually turn to our crystals highlight for you the
our crystals highlight for you the questions if you don't need to
询问是否不需要参数，并且它们是固定的
questions if you don't need to the parameters and they're fixed right
the parameters and they're fixed right depending on what your interest is if
如果您想要预测的分布，则取决于您的兴趣
depending on what your interest is if you want the predicted distributions the
you want the predicted distributions the floor where the questions will do is if
问题的基础是您是否想要将更多的东西向后
floor where the questions will do is if you want this more thing the backward
you want this more thing the backward will do it if you're gonna do the amount
如果您要做的是量，我们会做的，基本上我们必须做更多的事情
will do it if you're gonna do the amount we have to basically do more how can be
we have to basically do more how can be the lesson I'm gonna use the notation
我将使用Bishop的书中的符号来简化
the lesson I'm gonna use the notation from Bishop's book actually to simplify
from Bishop's book actually to simplify the notation for the you variables that
您拥有的变量的表示法，但事实是我们存在
the notation for the you variables that we had but the fact we there were
we had but the fact we there were nothing else but a constant term in the
除了这些分布的均值中的常数项，我
nothing else but a constant term in the the mean of these distributions I
the mean of these distributions I omitted here but actually if you can
此处省略，但实际上，如果您可以解决，则可以得到最终结果
omitted here but actually if you can solve you can take the final results in
solve you can take the final results in with a trivial trick you can discover
用一个简单的技巧，您可以发现您知道的修改问题
with a trivial trick you can discover the you know the modify the question
the you know the modify the question when there is an extra term of the means
当这里有额外的手段时，但现在专注于
when there is an extra term of the means here but right now concentrate on the
here but right now concentrate on the greatest or questioners look like right
最伟大或发问者看起来很正确，因此Rama会拒绝过渡
greatest or questioners look like right so a an Rama will decline the transition
so a an Rama will decline the transition model for the states and this is the
状态的模型，这是带有度量的观察模型
model for the states and this is the observation model with metrics it here
observation model with metrics it here Sigma and C n Sigma remember this
Sigma和C n Sigma记得这一点，因为我会忘记
Sigma and C n Sigma remember this because I will forget the and we will be
because I will forget the and we will be lost to the algebra okay so a and gamma
输给了代数好吧，所以我们应该从一些
lost to the algebra okay so a and gamma C and Sigma we supposed to from some
C and Sigma we supposed to from some initial state and so the initial state
初始状态，因此初始状态也将作为高斯给出
initial state and so the initial state is going to be given also as a Gaussian
is going to be given also as a Gaussian I mean we you can see actually later on
我的意思是，如果有时间，我们可以稍后在幻灯片中实际看到
I mean we you can see actually later on maybe in the slide if we have time and
maybe in the slide if we have time and remember I will let you know if this is
记住，我会让你知道这是否不是高斯混合
remember I will let you know if this is somehow not a Gaussian Gaussian mixture
somehow not a Gaussian Gaussian mixture then you don't get you get the different
那你就不会得到不同的方程式和正确的滤波，所以
then you don't get you get the different equations and kind of filtering right so
equations and kind of filtering right so this is not a job basically in to start
从高斯开始这基本上不是一项工作，否则您可能会进入
this is not a job basically in to start with a Gaussian otherwise you may get in
with a Gaussian otherwise you may get in trouble so mister questions basically if
麻烦，所以如果您不希望用书面形式提出问题，基本上可以提出一些疑问
trouble so mister questions basically if you don't want them in written in terms
you don't want them in written in terms of distributions you know this is how
您知道这就是问题的分布
of distributions you know this is how the questions look like they are all
the questions look like they are all linear right big asked why we call this
线性右大问为什么我们称其为线性动力学
linear right big asked why we call this a linear dynamical
a linear dynamical so later on we will actually if I don't
所以稍后，如果没有时间，我们将不得不阅读
so later on we will actually if I don't have time you would have to read it
have time you would have to read it right but we can expect this where for
是的，但是我们可以期望在这里，例如，而不是拥有
right but we can expect this where for example here rather than having
example here rather than having something a function of Z n minus 1
Z n减去1的函数，也许我们可以放Z n的函数f
something a function of Z n minus 1 maybe we can put some function f of Z n
maybe we can put some function f of Z n minus 1 or here some function G of Z ok
减1或此处的Z的某些函数G正常，但现在一切都在此处，
minus 1 or here some function G of Z ok but right now everything is in here and
but right now everything is in here and everything is gone
一切都消失了，所以很多参数正确了，所以从
everything is gone so a lot of parameters right so from the
so a lot of parameters right so from the dynamics basically we have a and gamma
动力学基本上我们有a和gamma从观察到我们有C和Sigma
dynamics basically we have a and gamma from the observation we have C and Sigma
from the observation we have C and Sigma and from the initial model you have mu 0
从初始模型中，您有mu 0和B 0，所以如果您想
and from the initial model you have mu 0 and B 0 so really if you want to
and B 0 so really if you want to complete the problem and do expectation
完成问题并基本实现期望最大化
complete the problem and do expectation maximization you need to basically
maximization you need to basically calculate all these parameters from
可以从观察中计算所有这些参数，从某种意义上讲，
calculate all these parameters from observations okay and in some sense this
observations okay and in some sense this is something at least in engineering
至少在工程学书籍中是这样，您将看到自己不认识任何人
is something at least in engineering books you will ever see you know nobody
books you will ever see you know nobody bothers to tell you how to compute these
麻烦告诉您如何计算这些参数，但实际上是这里的算法
bothers to tell you how to compute these parameters but really the algorithm here
parameters but really the algorithm here is just a simple application of e/m the
只是e / m的简单应用，就像我们使用隐藏的Markov一样
is just a simple application of e/m the same way we work with hidden Markov
same way we work with hidden Markov model ok derive the forward equations
确定模型就可以以某种方式导出此alpha消息的正向方程式
model ok derive the forward equations for this alpha messages and somehow
for this alpha messages and somehow let's discover that mr. questions are
让我们发现那个先生。问题真的是卡尔曼滤波方程，所以
let's discover that mr. questions are really the Kalman filter equations so
really the Kalman filter equations so we're going to do is since this is a
我们要做的是，因为这是算法的一部分，我要表示
we're going to do is since this is a part with algorithm I'm going to denote
part with algorithm I'm going to denote so everything's a Gaussian so I am going
所以一切都是高斯的，所以我将在Alpha消息中表示这些
so everything's a Gaussian so I am going to denote these for the Alpha message
to denote these for the Alpha message you know corresponding to state G n I'm
您知道对应于状态G n的意思是平均值和
you know corresponding to state G n I'm going to denote the mean and the
going to denote the mean and the variance is mu N and VN and the idea
方差是mu N和VN，想法是，我将从一个
variance is mu N and VN and the idea would be that I am going to start with a
would be that I am going to start with a master DN minus 1 so I'm going to know
主DN减1，所以我要知道这个MU减1和VN
master DN minus 1 so I'm going to know this mu n minus 1 and VN
this mu n minus 1 and VN one and then somehow using this for
一个，然后以某种方式将其用于增长消息传递方程式，我应该
one and then somehow using this for growth message-passing equation I should
growth message-passing equation I should be able to update new n minus 1 and DN
能够通过OK更新新的n减1和DN减1的联合国
be able to update new n minus 1 and DN minus 1 the UN and via ok
minus 1 the UN and via ok nothing major so basically what I have
没什么大不了的，所以基本上我所做的就是我采用了这个方程式
nothing major so basically what I have done is I took this equation and I
done is I took this equation and I expanded it by plugging in all the terms
通过插入所有术语来扩展它，而CN再次记得确实不是
expanded it by plugging in all the terms still CN remember again is really not
still CN remember again is really not necessary sometimes confusing but to
有时会令人困惑，但要使其成为一个等号，您需要
necessary sometimes confusing but to make this an equal sign you need that so
make this an equal sign you need that so this is the mr. x this Gaussian okay the
这是先生。 x这是高斯式的，观察模型很清楚
this is the mr. x this Gaussian okay the observation model is clear the message
observation model is clear the message at n minus 1 is there so we suppose we
在n减1处，所以我们假设我们知道这一点，这就是过渡
at n minus 1 is there so we suppose we know this and this is the transition
know this and this is the transition model looks like that ends the N minus 1
模型看起来像这样结束了N减1的积分，所以再次
model looks like that ends the N minus 1 is integrated off ok so again the
is integrated off ok so again the problem is given this because we will do
给这个问题是因为我们将在前进的过程中做到这一点
problem is given this because we will do it this as we go forward
it this as we go forward we want to compute that okay
我们要计算没关系
如果我们想适当地使用这些方程式，则需要一个过程
it this as we go forward we want to compute that okay
and a sponson in the process if we want to have these equations properly
如果我们想适当地使用这些方程式，则需要一个过程
to have these equations properly normalized we will need to update these
归一化，我们将需要在这里更新这些系数，好吧，我是
normalized we will need to update these coefficients here as well all right I am
coefficients here as well all right I am going to take highlight as much as I can
我会建议所有其他人都将尽我所能来突出我的意思
going to take highlight as much as I can all right the rest i really suggest that
all right the rest i really suggest that you do it as a homework okay put in
您可以将其作为作业完成，可以将高程动脉放在幻灯片中的幻灯片上
you do it as a homework okay put in elevation arteries on the slides in the
elevation arteries on the slides in the slides but I want you to just copy this
幻灯片，但我希望您仅复制此公式即可
slides but I want you to just copy this formula is actually going to either
formula is actually going to either because you learned about manipulative
因为您了解了有关高伯利（Woodbury）身份的操纵性高斯人
because you learned about manipulative gaussians about the Woodbury identity
gaussians about the Woodbury identity marginalization conditionals Vegas rule
边缘化有条件拉斯维加斯统治一切
marginalization conditionals Vegas rule everything is there
everything is there how can you go wrong okay so so when we
你怎么会出问题好吧，所以当我们第一次来的时候，我要看看这个
how can you go wrong okay so so when we are this first I'm going to look at this
are this first I'm going to look at this list
列出这不是增长是这个不可或缺的
list this ain't a grow is this integral in
this ain't a grow is this integral in the ocean and why the whole integral and
海洋以及为什么整体和它是来自各种魔术的高斯
the ocean and why the whole integral and it is a Gaussian from kinds of magical
it is a Gaussian from kinds of magical are coming to be Gaussian white set out
当我们来到这里时，将成为高斯白色，列出了发光物
are coming to be Gaussian white set out listing the glow when we are here on
listing the glow when we are here on this integral
这个积分
我有两个高斯的乘积，但其中之一的最小值是线性的
listing the glow when we are here on this integral
I have the product of two gaussians but the min of one of them right is linear
所以这非常非常重，就像给定X的概率为Y
so it's very very heaviest is like having a probability of Y given X all
having a probability of Y given X all right but this linear in X times the
是的，但是X的线性乘以X的概率，我要问的是
right but this linear in X times the probability of X and what I'm asking is
probability of X and what I'm asking is to find the probability of Y when I
在我正确整合X时找到Y的概率，因为我不会
to find the probability of Y when I integrate X out right because I won't
integrate X out right because I won't see n minus 1 out right so basically
看到n减1就好了，基本上这就像有关节
see n minus 1 out right so basically this is like having the Joint
this is like having the Joint Distribution of two versions then you
然后分配两个版本，您想多角色撒谎
Distribution of two versions then you want to multi-role lies
want to multi-role lies okay so the idea is this is the formula
好的，所以这是我剪切并粘贴到所有地方的公式
okay so the idea is this is the formula that I cut and paste it not everywhere
that I cut and paste it not everywhere but you guys will do the algebra and you
但是你们会做代数的，您会比我学得更好的，所以这里是
but you guys will do the algebra and you will learn it better than me so here is
will learn it better than me so here is like having Congress to distribution px
就像让国会分配px可以，这是给定的
like having Congress to distribution px all right this is given this is given
all right this is given this is given all right hold this P of Y given X all
好吧，给定X好，保持Y的P不变，您会发现平均值是线性的
all right hold this P of Y given X all right and you notice the mean is linear
right and you notice the mean is linear in X which is the N minus 1 you see that
在X的N减1中，您会看到Sigma Y中没有
in X which is the N minus 1 you see that there's not be here in the Sigma Y of
there's not be here in the Sigma Y of course is this gamma so from my
当然是这个伽玛，所以从我的信息来看，这是高斯
course is this gamma so from my information of this for in a Gaussian
information of this for in a Gaussian models P of Y comes to be this nice
Y的模型P就是这个很好的分布，这意味着您
models P of Y comes to be this nice distribution that just mean that you
distribution that just mean that you securely has variance that we've set up
安全地存在差异，我们已经建立了您不需要证明它们的服务
securely has variance that we've set up the service you don't need to prove them
the service you don't need to prove them you pull the mouse égalité and and you
您拉动鼠标égalité，然后与它们一起工作好吧，请确保当您看到
you pull the mouse égalité and and you work with them okay be sure when you see
work with them okay be sure when you see them the first time in a textbook we
我们在教科书中第一次使用它们，是因为在
them the first time in a textbook we derive them because a little mistake in
derive them because a little mistake in the textbook we mess up the rest of your
这本教科书使您的余生变得一团糟，我很容易看到这一点，因为
the textbook we mess up the rest of your lives and I can easily see that because
lives and I can easily see that because I've seen those mistakes in textbooks
我已经用最常见的公式在教科书中看到了这些错误，所以
I've seen those mistakes in textbooks all right in the most common formula so
all right in the most common formula so so why is given like that right so this
那么为什么赋予这样的权利，所以这个积分我可以写成高斯型
so why is given like that right so this integral I can write it as a Gaussian
integral I can write it as a Gaussian that looks like that and he comes
看起来像这样，他来的意思是均值是m n减去1
that looks like that and he comes that the mean is a times mu n minus 1
that the mean is a times mu n minus 1 and the variance is P n minus 1 where
并且方差是P n减去1，其中方差是
and the variance is P n minus 1 where the variance is written by this is
the variance is written by this is coming up from this nice form
从这个很好的形式出现好吧，你不必相信我
coming up from this nice form okay you don't have to believe me
okay you don't have to believe me because this is the variance you plug it
因为这就是您插入的差异，这就是您所能接受的
because this is the variance you plug it in and that's what you get okay
in and that's what you get okay all right so obviously I'm putting n
好吧，所以很明显我在这里放n减1，因为你知道
all right so obviously I'm putting n minus 1 here everything because you know
minus 1 here everything because you know you know this whole divided was fairly
你知道这个整体除以时间减去-1是合理的，所以我们称其为
you know this whole divided was fairly for the time and minus 1 so we call this
for the time and minus 1 so we call this intermediate mathematics PN minus 1 okay
中级数学PN减1好的
所以这个积分是Z的决定，所以这个触手是
for the time and minus 1 so we call this intermediate mathematics PN minus 1 okay
so this integral it comes out to be a decision in Z so this tentacle is an
所以这个积分是Z的决定，所以这个触手是
decision in Z so this tentacle is an arginine shell and what is this thing
精氨酸壳，今天这是什么东西，在某种程度上是高斯的
arginine shell and what is this thing today is a Gaussian in extent that has
today is a Gaussian in extent that has immense linear function of Z so what can
Z的巨大线性函数，那么我们该怎么做，我们需要做两件事
immense linear function of Z so what can we do we need to do two things right we
we do we need to do two things right we need basically to complete the posterior
基本上需要完成这个后验，所以这里不是边缘化
need basically to complete the posterior of this so here is not marginalization
of this so here is not marginalization what we need to do is sort of from P of
我们需要做的是从给定Y的X的P到给定X的Y的P
what we need to do is sort of from P of X given Y go to P of Y given X all right
X given Y go to P of Y given X all right and this proficiency well is really feel
这个熟练程度真的很难做到归一化因子还可以
and this proficiency well is really feel fractious the normalization factor okay
fractious the normalization factor okay so so what when so tell us what you need
所以什么时候告诉我们您需要什么，您知道您知道吗，我正在使用这个
so so what when so tell us what you need you know you know perfect I'm using this
you know you know perfect I'm using this generic notation and P of Y effects and
通用符号和P的Y效应，我们需要将其反转，我们需要
generic notation and P of Y effects and we need to invert this and we need to
we need to invert this and we need to compute P of X given Y and that is given
在给定Y的情况下计算X的P，并由该均值的该形式表示，并且
compute P of X given Y and that is given by this nice formal of this mean and
by this nice formal of this mean and this variance right and
这种差异权利和
实际上，正如我所写下的那样，他们没有使用这些差异
by this nice formal of this mean and this variance right and
and actually there is as I've written down they don't use these variances you
实际上，正如我所写下的那样，他们没有使用这些差异
down they don't use these variances you see here all right what the use is they
好的，在这里看到它们的用途是什么，它们赋予伍德伯里（Woodbury）身份，如果
see here all right what the use is they gives the Woodbury identity where if you
gives the Woodbury identity where if you complete this all right you can simplify
正确完成此操作后，您可以简化为PN减去1减去J n乘以T
complete this all right you can simplify to actually PN minus 1 minus J n times T
to actually PN minus 1 minus J n times T P and minus 1 for Tyrion comes to this
P和减号1代表提利昂（Tyrion），我知道您忘了，但这个KN是
P and minus 1 for Tyrion comes to this and I know you forgot but this KN it is
and I know you forgot but this KN it is identical to what we derived in the last
与我们在上一堂课中获得的结果相同，即J列增益
identical to what we derived in the last lecture which is the column J gain
lecture which is the column J gain matrix okay so in this coefficient Sigma
矩阵好，所以在这个系数Sigma n好
matrix okay so in this coefficient Sigma n okay
n okay which is basically least marginal
这基本上是边际效应最小，也是高斯效应
which is basically least marginal effects and it's also a Gaussian that
effects and it's also a Gaussian that comes later okay
以后再来没关系，对Sigma n的兴趣不大，但是
comes later okay again one less interested on Sigma n but
again one less interested on Sigma n but if we want to make that equation to be
如果我们想使等式具有等号，则必须
if we want to make that equation to be to have an equal sign right it has to
to have an equal sign right it has to look like that this the normalization
看起来像是归一化因子，所以看这个等式
look like that this the normalization factor and so look at this equation so
factor and so look at this equation so let me just remind you what we compute
让我提醒您，我们正确计算的是平均值
let me just remind you what we compute it right what we computed is the mean
it right what we computed is the mean and variance of the alpha methods and
方法的方差和方差，最优化是过滤
and variance of the alpha methods and the optimises is the filtering
the optimises is the filtering distribution of Z F and the president
ZF的分布和总统分布是Zn的概率
distribution of Z F and the president distribution is the probability of Zn
distribution is the probability of Zn given the data x1 to X label that okay
给定数据x1至X标签，可以
所以这是平均值，这是此过滤分布可以
distribution is the probability of Zn given the data x1 to X label that okay
so this is the mean alright this is the mean for this filtering distribution can
所以这是平均值，这是此过滤分布可以
mean for this filtering distribution can you put this term physical meaning to
您将这个术语的物理含义用于Vista问题，以便我们了解一些
you put this term physical meaning to Vista question so that if we have some
Vista question so that if we have some physical meaning then you can write the
物理意义上的话，您可以凭直觉而不是直觉来写等式
physical meaning then you can write the equation from intuition rather than
equation from intuition rather than algebra so what is a times nu n minus 1
代数，所以n n减1的时间是多少
所以您基本上采用10-1的打印分布
equation from intuition rather than algebra so what is a times nu n minus 1
so you take basically the printing distribution of 10-1
所以您基本上采用10-1的打印分布
distribution of 10-1 and you push fun with the mean with the
然后用转换矩阵a推平均值，就可以了
and you push fun with the mean with the transition matrix a you sit up okay
transition matrix a you sit up okay so that's what it is and now we have
就是这样，现在我们有了这个增益矩阵乘以一些误差，
so that's what it is and now we have this gain matrix times some error and
this gain matrix times some error and that error is the observation that you
该错误是您突然看到的观察结果，您看到的是您的数据
that error is the observation that you saw suddenly you see data that's your
saw suddenly you see data that's your observational time n right and what is C
观察时间n对，C是个a子，-叔叔你刚刚告诉我，
observational time n right and what is C a mule and - you just told me that
a mule and - you just told me that a mu n minus 1 is this transy is pushing
一个n减1是这个转移正在推动先前的均值与
a mu n minus 1 is this transy is pushing forward the previous mean with the
forward the previous mean with the transition matrix a so what is G times a
过渡矩阵a，所以G是新的n减去1的乘积，就没有观察到
transition matrix a so what is G times a new n minus 1 it's got no observation on
new n minus 1 it's got no observation on that you will have and this is really
您将拥有的，而这实际上是另一种有效和有效的方法
that you will have and this is really the other what to do and effectively
the other what to do and effectively before you have a landing matrix which
在您有一个着陆矩阵之前，它就是这个常见的增益矩阵，所以k
before you have a landing matrix which is this common gain matrix right so k
is this common gain matrix right so k times this error plus the first pair
这个错误加上第一对给您新的均值，
times this error plus the first pair gives you the new updated mean and
gives you the new updated mean and that's right out okay first you know
没关系，首先您知道这很容易记住，但是您不知道
that's right out okay first you know this is easy to remember but you do not
this is easy to remember but you do not remember that actually the exact
请记住，实际上这个增益矩阵的确切学习矩阵是
remember that actually the exact learning matrix this gain matrix is
learning matrix this gain matrix is given by anything like that but you know
由这样的东西给，但你知道我们最终知道的日子
given by anything like that but you know what at the end of the days we know for
what at the end of the days we know for stochastic optimization it doesn't
随机优化在其他方面并没有多大关系
stochastic optimization it doesn't really matter in other ways if you put
really matter in other ways if you put something else and you start iterating
其他的事情，你开始迭代，你会给正确的答案紧张
something else and you start iterating you will give the right answer straining
you will give the right answer straining waste okay but if we want to do things
浪费吧，但是如果我们想精确地做事，这就是名字的样子
waste okay but if we want to do things exactly and this is how the name looks
exactly and this is how the name looks of the variance and house here you need
方差和房子的位置，您需要启动算法并迅速采取
of the variance and house here you need to start the algorithm and swiftly take
to start the algorithm and swiftly take the rest is passing on the first step
剩下的就是第一步，第一个消息基本上需要
the rest is passing on the first step the first message basically requires the
the first message basically requires the initial state to the probability of Z 1
初始状态的概率为Z乘以第一次测量的1倍
initial state to the probability of Z 1 times the first measurement that you do
times the first measurement that you do so this is our first P of Z 1 this is
这是Z 1的第一个P这是发射
so this is our first P of Z 1 this is the emission
the emission of x1 okay so if you plug in actually
x1还可以，所以如果您实际上插入了以下插件，那么它们是有福的，或者
of x1 okay so if you plug in actually following the same ones are blessed or
following the same ones are blessed or messes passing its to through to the
弄乱了它通过代数，因为你没有任何
messes passing its to through to the algebra because you don't have any
algebra because you don't have any integral anything like that here is muon
积分之类的东西是muon，这是v1以及我们的常数
integral anything like that here is muon and here is v1 and the constants to our
and here is v1 and the constants to our scanner like that okay so you have a way
这样的扫描仪还可以，所以您有一种启动算法的方法，然后
scanner like that okay so you have a way to start the algorithm and and then if
to start the algorithm and and then if you use the update formulas and that's
您使用更新公式，这就是问题并完成了
you use the update formulas and that's the come up into the questions and done
the come up into the questions and done okay in you know in a few minutes we
好吧，几分钟后，我们基本上完成了彩色滤光片的制作
okay in you know in a few minutes we basically finished with a color filter
basically finished with a color filter questions using ideas of masters party
用大师党的思想提问
只是一个小型的图形表示形式，您可以
basically finished with a color filter questions using ideas of masters party
just a mini are sort of a graphical representation of the way that you
只是一个小型的图形表示形式，您可以
representation of the way that you compute this printing distributions so I
计算这个打印分布，所以我认为，我认为这就是我们得出的结果
compute this printing distributions so I think and I think this is how we derive
think and I think this is how we derive these things last week so this is the
这些东西是上周的，所以这是n减1的打印分布，然后
these things last week so this is the printing distribution of n minus 1 then
printing distribution of n minus 1 then you use the transition model basically
您使用的过渡模型基本上是由给定的Zn概率定义的
you use the transition model basically defined by this probability of Zn given
defined by this probability of Zn given Zn minus 1 so you update basically
锌减1，所以基本上更新州际公路的终点仍然是
Zn minus 1 so you update basically interstate is the end still using the
interstate is the end still using the measurements from x1 to xn minus 1 so
从x1到xn减去1的测量值，所以这就像吸积模型，
measurements from x1 to xn minus 1 so this is like an accretion model and the
this is like an accretion model and the values of this dictates basically a
该值基本上决定了分布范围
values of this dictates basically a distribution that has is much wider in
distribution that has is much wider in support from the splintering stage at n
分裂阶段的支持为n减1，然后有效地得到什么
support from the splintering stage at n minus 1 and then effectively what to get
minus 1 and then effectively what to get the filtering state at time n you
您基本上必须将时间n处的过滤状态乘以
the filtering state at time n you basically have to multiply with the
basically have to multiply with the observation model ok that looks like
好的观察模型，看起来像这样，最终非常广泛
observation model ok that looks like this and eventually this very broad
this and eventually this very broad push forward apply for one step
向前申请一个步骤，以预测现在该位置已被修改
push forward apply for one step predicting this position now is modified
predicting this position now is modified to give you to give you this good
给你，给你这种良好的分布是
to give you to give you this good distribution that is the
distribution that is the take the time that so basically again
花费时间，这样基本上又是一步一步的预测，您就知道了，
take the time that so basically again one-step prediction you know ahead and
one-step prediction you know ahead and then you collect the measurement accent
然后收集测量重点，并使用此模型进行更新
then you collect the measurement accent and you update with this model for a
and you update with this model for a minute efficiency it gives you and you
微小的效率，它使您和您都有权利说话，所以现在我们
minute efficiency it gives you and you get the right to talk alright so now we
get the right to talk alright so now we have to discuss the backward message
必须讨论反向传递的消息，我想快速执行此操作，因为
have to discuss the backward message passing I wanna do this fast because
passing I wanna do this fast because basically the question is look the same
基本上问题是一样的，好吧，您只会对此感兴趣
basically the question is look the same okay you will only be interested from
okay you will only be interested from this backward passing for getting this
向后传递以获得此平滑方程式，但我不认为我
this backward passing for getting this smoothing equations but I don't think I
smoothing equations but I don't think I cover or maybe it was in last two
也许是上一讲的最后两秒钟，所以我们
cover or maybe it was in last two seconds from the previous lecture so we
seconds from the previous lecture so we need to get the smoothing distributions
需要获得平滑分布的潜力，我提醒您，我们有
need to get the smoothing distributions potential I remind you that we have
potential I remind you that we have defined as gamma messages okay as the
定义为伽马消息，因为每个消息的乘积都在
defined as gamma messages okay as the product of the message is coming at each
product of the message is coming at each node so the product of alpha and beta
节点，因此alpha和beta的乘积以及此gamma消息定义了
node so the product of alpha and beta and this gamma messages define the
and this gamma messages define the sufficient statistics that we need of
EM算法需要的足够统计信息
sufficient statistics that we need of the EM algorithm
the EM algorithm okay and we were breaking discussed me
好吧，我们一言不发地讨论了我
okay and we were breaking discussed me in one word
in one word well today all right so the debate looks
今天很好，所以辩论看起来像我们基本上必须去
well today all right so the debate looks like that we basically have to go
like that we basically have to go backward we'd have to start to the last
倒退，我们必须开始到最后一个，所以十加一才能完成大师
backward we'd have to start to the last so ten plus one to complete the master
so ten plus one to complete the master then I have defined exactly the message
那么我已经在这里准确定义了消息，以便这是平等的，包括
then I have defined exactly the message here so that this is equality including
here so that this is equality including the closeness of the heft and again you
紧密的距离，您可以再次回顾上一讲
the closeness of the heft and again you can look back on the previous lecture
can look back on the previous lecture but I had this equation that we
但是我有这个方程，我们可以标准化我们的标准化形式
but I had this equation that we normalize our normalized form okay this
normalize our normalized form okay this is is precisely God so and again what's
恰恰是上帝，更大的信息的意义是
is is precisely God so and again what's the meaning of the bigger message is the
the meaning of the bigger message is the probability of sending observations to
发送给xn的观测值的概率加1到x杯的长度，给定
probability of sending observations to xn plus 1 to x cup the length given that
xn plus 1 to x cup the length given that I started third Zn at some value okay so
我以一定的价值开始使用第三个锌，所以这有点美国
I started third Zn at some value okay so that's the bit America
我记得我给你答案博客，但是基本上你需要做的是
I remember I give you the answer blog but basically what you need to do is
but basically what you need to do is take the since everything is a Gaussian
拿，因为一切都是高斯，让我看看我们要假设
take the since everything is a Gaussian let me see we're going to assume that
let me see we're going to assume that this bigger message this is a given
这个更大的消息，这是给定的任何地方
this bigger message this is a given anywhere
好吧，所以我们有这个好吧，我们知道我们有我们知道我们知道
all right so we have this okay we know that we have that we know that we know
that we have that we know that we know the update from the alpha messengers we
来自Alpha Messenger的更新，我们清楚地知道了我的皮肤
the update from the alpha messengers we know the skin obviously where I have
know the skin obviously where I have this rather than giving you the little
而不是给您一点本质，而实际上如果它不在
this rather than giving you the little essence it and actually if it is not in
essence it and actually if it is not in the slides maybe that's an external
幻灯片可能是明确暗示
the slides maybe that's an external hormone to the idea of explicitly the
hormone to the idea of explicitly the bit of assistance or the bus was moving
一点帮助，或者公交车正在移动彩色过滤方程式，所以这
bit of assistance or the bus was moving color filtering equations okay so this
color filtering equations okay so this peg will I have is the combined message
我要钉的是派生消息中合并的消息部门beta，但如果
peg will I have is the combined message Department beta in the derivation but if
Department beta in the derivation but if you only use this to compute this beta
您只能使用它来计算此Beta消息谢谢您，很好，您已经获得了
you only use this to compute this beta messages thank you good you get this the
messages thank you good you get this the smoothing distributions so what I have
平滑分布，所以我在这里将伽玛定义为
smoothing distributions so what I have here is I defined the gamma to be a
here is I defined the gamma to be a Gaussian with mean this new and Hart and
高斯与这个新的和哈特和V和哈特的意思是，你可以知道
Gaussian with mean this new and Hart and V and Hart and you can show by you know
V and Hart and you can show by you know if actually what you need to do is
如果实际上您需要做的是将这个乘以R例如所有
if actually what you need to do is multiply this with an R for instance all
multiply this with an R for instance all right so you can get the Rommel essence
正确，这样您就可以获得左侧的Rommel本质，然后插入所有内容
right so you can get the Rommel essence of the left and then plug in everything
of the left and then plug in everything you know on the right everything is a
你知道在右边一切都是高斯的，这是最终答案
you know on the right everything is a Gaussian and here is the final answer
Gaussian and here is the final answer the mean and the variance for the gamma
伽玛抗蚀剂的均值和方差是
the mean and the variance for the gamma resist is the mean and the variance that
resist is the mean and the variance that we computed for the Alpha messages times
我们计算的Alpha消息乘以这是均值和方差1
we computed for the Alpha messages times this are the mean and the variance one
this are the mean and the variance one step ahead right because these are
向右前进，因为这些是向后的方程式减去alpha nu n
step ahead right because these are backwards equations minus alpha nu n
backwards equations minus alpha nu n minus P n but we derive it in this
减去P n，但是我们在这个矩阵J中得到它，这里得到V n乘以a
minus P n but we derive it in this matrix J and here is given V n times a
matrix J and here is given V n times a transpose B n minus
换位B n减去好，所以一个很好的方程式，我认为
transpose B n minus okay so a very nice equation and I think
okay so a very nice equation and I think bits of the equations actually for the
如果您在
bits of the equations actually for the carbons moving algorithm if you see in
carbons moving algorithm if you see in the notes basically you will immediately
笔记基本上，您将立即认识到您需要解决的问题
the notes basically you will immediately recognize what the questions you need to
recognize what the questions you need to so coming out of this alright
所以走出来可以应用这个方程式或给你
so coming out of this alright to apply this equations or give you the
to apply this equations or give you the gamma Leicester's obviously you have
伽玛·莱斯特（Gamma Leicester）显然是您必须首先运用地址的力量
gamma Leicester's obviously you have first to run the power of addresses
first to run the power of addresses passing together nu + V and then go
传递nu + V，然后向后退以计算伽玛
passing together nu + V and then go backwards to calculate gamma okay
backwards to calculate gamma okay alright so you have to blossom in
好吧，所以你必须按顺序开花，现在又有一个
alright so you have to blossom in sequence now there is one more
sequence now there is one more distribution that you need to get on the
您需要播出的发行版Margaret记住，记住这一点
distribution that you need to get on the air Margaret remember that remember this
air Margaret remember that remember this weird distribution the joint
奇怪的分布Zn减去1 CL的联合分布
weird distribution the joint distribution of Zn minus 1 CL that comes
distribution of Zn minus 1 CL that comes with the first one we did it apply the
对于第一个，我们执行了隐藏顺序
with the first one we did it apply the hidden order
hidden order am L going from the hmm order okay so we
我是从hmm阶开始的吗，所以我们需要计算这个联合
am L going from the hmm order okay so we will need to compute this joint
will need to compute this joint distribution for staining of Zn -
锌的染色分布-Rollins yeah是的，还有
distribution for staining of Zn - Rollins yeah all right and there are
Rollins yeah all right and there are multiple ways of doing it you know and
您知道多种方式，这显然是最简单的方法
multiple ways of doing it you know and here obviously the most trivial way to
here obviously the most trivial way to do it is to take the masters to derive
是不是要让大师们得出，所以不小于负1和alpha消息
do it is to take the masters to derive so no than minus 1 and alpha message
so no than minus 1 and alpha message that the message that I should not beat
我不应该从右边打败的信息，然后与
that the message that I should not beat up from right and then multiply with the
up from right and then multiply with the transition model and the observation
过渡模型和观察模型，这将为您提供
transition model and the observation model and that will give you this
model and that will give you this distribution so when you plug in all the
分布，所以当您插入所有分布时，出来的却是
distribution so when you plug in all the distributions where it comes out is but
distributions where it comes out is but the joint distribution of Zn minus n CN
Zn减去n CN的联合分布是nu n减去1微米我提醒你这些
the joint distribution of Zn minus n CN is nu n minus 1 mu n I remind you these
is nu n minus 1 mu n I remind you these are the means for the gamma messages
是伽马信息正常的手段，核心受众是J n减去
are the means for the gamma messages okay and the core audience is J n minus
okay and the core audience is J n minus 1 times these variants of the gamma
这些伽玛方法的变体的1倍和
1 times these variants of the gamma methods and
methods and the J metrics some priority is given by
J指标对此有一些优先权，所以让我理解
the J metrics some priority is given by this okay so let me understand that
this okay so let me understand that equations are easy right but you know if
等式很容易，但是您知道您是否想编写计算机程序
equations are easy right but you know if you think of writing a computer program
you think of writing a computer program that implements this it's basically once
基本上，一旦您输入了他们的分析表达式，
that implements this it's basically once you put their analytical expressions the
you put their analytical expressions the whole algorithm is basically ten lines
整个算法基本上是十行，实际上是西班牙，我的意思是如果您搜索
whole algorithm is basically ten lines and literally Spain I mean if you search
and literally Spain I mean if you search on the web and you download the color
在网络上，您下载了彩色滤光片算法，因为它有十盏灯，因为
on the web and you download the color filter algorithm it's ten lights because
filter algorithm it's ten lights because every do you know the MATLAB knows how
您都知道MATLAB知道如何操纵高斯，但您却不知道
every do you know the MATLAB knows how to manipulate gaussians and you don't
to manipulate gaussians and you don't have to do much you give the exact
您必须做很多事情才能给出确切的表达，剩下的就是历史
have to do much you give the exact expressions and the rest is history
expressions and the rest is history okay I mean they become how we're going
好的，我的意思是，既然我们
okay I mean they become how we're going to get all these parameters now that we
to get all these parameters now that we got the sufficient statistics for you
得到了足够的统计信息以及其他足够的统计信息
got the sufficient statistics for you know with other sufficient statistics
know with other sufficient statistics for this from this gamma messages so I
为此，请通过伽玛消息，让我提醒您我们需要做的事情，
for this from this gamma messages so I remind you what we need to do and let
remind you what we need to do and let somebody remind me so what we supposed
有人提醒我，所以我们应该做的是我们是否愿意接受，所以
somebody remind me so what we supposed to do yes whether we will we take so the
to do yes whether we will we take so the expectation of what
对什么的期望
联合对数似然性，所以我们基本上认为只有结果
to do yes whether we will we take so the expectation of what
the joint log-likelihood so we will take basically there's only like if result
联合对数似然性，所以我们基本上认为只有结果
basically there's only like if result observations and hidden variables
观察值和隐藏变量，因为这是非常容易的分布
observations and hidden variables because what's a very easy distribution
because what's a very easy distribution right Gaussian basically easy to write
正确的高斯基本上很容易写下来，特别是长的，因为
right Gaussian basically easy to write down especially the long and because we
down especially the long and because we don't know z we will take the
不知道z，我们会相对于
don't know z we will take the expectation of that with respect to the
expectation of that with respect to the posterior of the Samadhi
在Samadhi的后部，所以要做的不是一步
posterior of the Samadhi so rather than a step to do that
so rather than a step to do that computation with all the parameters
固定所有参数的计算各不相同，然后一次
computation with all the parameters fixed are variously to all and then once
fixed are variously to all and then once we compute out so that we prepare to be
我们进行计算，以便准备成为足够的统计数据，因为
we compute out so that we prepare to be sufficient statistics because that
sufficient statistics because that expectation with respect to the
关于Z右后方的期望将获得
expectation with respect to the posterior of Z right will acquire the
posterior of Z right will acquire the mean of Z and you know the C variables
Z的均值，您知道我们之前看到的C变量，所以这是
mean of Z and you know the C variables that we saw before so that's part of the
that we saw before so that's part of the step and in the m-step basically we are
一步，在m步中，我们基本上将取导数
step and in the m-step basically we are going to take derivatives with respect
going to take derivatives with respect to the theta parameters and will provide
到theta参数，并将提供更新，这里的三个参数是
to the theta parameters and will provide update and the three parameters here are
update and the three parameters here are sort of elastic because we have one two
一种弹性的，因为我们在一个向量中有一个1 2 3 4 5矩阵
sort of elastic because we have one two three four five matrices in one vector
three four five matrices in one vector okay the next thing is you will see that
好吧，接下来的事情是，您将看到方程式实际上是解耦的
okay the next thing is you will see that the equations actually decouple and in
the equations actually decouple and in almost in a trivial way they look like
几乎以一种微不足道的方式，他们看起来像我正在做很多这样的矩阵
almost in a trivial way they look like I'm making a lot of these matrices like
I'm making a lot of these matrices like the covariances like you know gamma and
像您知道的伽玛和西格玛的协方差，您会发现它看起来几乎
the covariances like you know gamma and Sigma you will see that it looks almost
Sigma you will see that it looks almost like working with estimating the mean
就像估算多元变量的均值和方差一样
like working with estimating the mean and the variance of a multivariate
and the variance of a multivariate Gaussian so basically doing Emily
高斯，所以基本上对多元高斯做Emily估计
Gaussian so basically doing Emily estimate for the multivariate Gaussian
estimate for the multivariate Gaussian and as you know what you do Emily you
而且，如您所知，艾米丽（Emily）基本上就得到了
and as you know what you do Emily you basically get the sample mean of the
basically get the sample mean of the sample variance okay so this is the
样本方差还可以，所以这是我们需要的足够的统计量
sample variance okay so this is the sufficient statistic that we need right
sufficient statistic that we need right the expectation of Zn
锌的期望，我们已经完成了
the expectation of Zn we already completed it
我们需要这个，记得这个联合认为你知道
we need the this remember this joint thinks you know
this remember this joint thinks you know we need the expectation of Z and Z and
我们需要Z和Z的期望值，并且减去一个帖子，因此您可以
we need the expectation of Z and Z and minus one post post so you can since you
minus one post post so you can since you know the distribution of the joint the
知道关节的分布负1时z LZ的关节分布
know the distribution of the joint the joint distribution of z LZ at minus 1
joint distribution of z LZ at minus 1 this will be the body also that this
这也将是身体，这种关系
this will be the body also that this relation
relation - unit responds and then of course you
-设备响应，那么您当然需要TN z和
- unit responds and then of course you will need the expectation of TN z and
will need the expectation of TN z and transpose that is given like that and
像这样给定的移调和我们刚才计算的所有这些方
transpose that is given like that and all of these parties we just computed
all of these parties we just computed all right so this will be can be sort of
好的，所以这可以是美学上的那种
all right so this will be can be sort of that in the aesthetic
that in the aesthetic so the not like equal to it's a trivial
所以不等于等于是微不足道的，因为你知道你有最初的
so the not like equal to it's a trivial because you know you have the initial
because you know you have the initial observation model I mean the initial
观察模型我的意思是初始状态模型，然后是过渡
observation model I mean the initial state model and then the transition and
state model and then the transition and the measurement and these are gaussians
测量值和这些都是高斯值，所以我们将采用较长的子串
the measurement and these are gaussians so we'll take long substring just
so we'll take long substring just simplify the trivial matter
简化琐碎的事情，这就是我们需要计算的需求
simplify the trivial matter so this is what we need to compute need
so this is what we need to compute need to take the joint of likelihood and take
对可能性采取联合行动，并期望
to take the joint of likelihood and take the expectation with respect to
the expectation with respect to parameters are showing the expectation
参数显示相对于z变量保持的期望
parameters are showing the expectation with respect to the z variables keeping
with respect to the z variables keeping the parameters fixed so let's do sort of
固定的参数，让我们对它进行一些琐碎的应用
the parameters fixed so let's do sort of a trivial application of this to
a trivial application of this to computing new 0 and p 0 i remind you
计算新的0和p 0我提醒您，这些是均值和方差
computing new 0 and p 0 i remind you those are the mean and variance for the
those are the mean and variance for the initial state okay so basically in that
初始状态还可以，所以基本上是在准备似然联合
initial state okay so basically in that preparation of the joint of likelihood
preparation of the joint of likelihood only this term will give the
仅此一项将为此处涉及的人员做出贡献0
only this term will give the contribution for the involved in here 0
contribution for the involved in here 0 0 and really I mean estimating easier to
0，实际上我的意思是估计更容易达到0就像多元变量的Emily
0 and really I mean estimating easier to 0 is like an Emily for multivariate
0 is like an Emily for multivariate Gaussian right I mean it's identical
高斯对，我的意思是完全一样，所以当您撰写本文时，请展开
Gaussian right I mean it's identical okay so when you write you expand this
okay so when you write you expand this this is what you get right
这是你做对的事情，与做艾米丽（Emily）的唯一区别
this is what you get right the only difference from doing Emily of
the only difference from doing Emily of multi-value Gaussian here is an
多值高斯在这里是对Z的期望
multi-value Gaussian here is an expectation with respect to the Z
expectation with respect to the Z variables so you notice the expectation
变量，因此您会注意到参与的期望
variables so you notice the expectation with involved
with involved you know z1 transposing one in also
您知道z1换位也期望Z 1诗句的
you know z1 transposing one in also expectation of Z 1 verse of the
expectation of Z 1 verse of the sufficient statistic that I saw before
我之前看到的足够的统计量，所以z1对Z 1和Z的期望是
sufficient statistic that I saw before so z1 expectation of Z 1 and Z ones you
so z1 expectation of Z 1 and Z ones you want to expose so you have altered and
想暴露出来，所以您已经改变了，所以当这些是您的统计数据时，
want to expose so you have altered and so when so these are the statistics you
so when so these are the statistics you need to compute okay and in the end step
需要计算好，最后，第四步是关于
need to compute okay and in the end step four is the maximization with respect to
four is the maximization with respect to the 0 and p 0 which the same thing as
具有抗病毒高斯的0和p 0基本相同
the 0 and p 0 which the same thing as have antiviral gaussian and basically
have antiviral gaussian and basically these are the results that you get
这些都是您可以接受的结果，因此主要和
these are the results that you get okay so the the updates of the main and
okay so the the updates of the main and the valiant are given basically actually
英勇实际上是根据足够的统计数据给出的
the valiant are given basically actually in terms of the sufficient statistics
in terms of the sufficient statistics because I mean this destructive expected
因为我的意思是，这种破坏性的预期结果还可以，就像
because I mean this destructive expected result here ok these are again like the
result here ok these are again like the sample mean right and this is like the
样本均值对，这就像样本主体对他们的期望一样
sample mean right and this is like the sample body right the expectations them
sample body right the expectations them so far of something okay
到目前为止，很快就可以了，您知道是否要
so far of something okay very fast you know if you want to
very fast you know if you want to calculate for example a and gamma okay
计算例如a和gamma好吧，您需要扩展此术语，以便
calculate for example a and gamma okay you need to expand this term so to
you need to expand this term so to expand it you can get something like
扩展它，你可以得到像这样的东西
expand it you can get something like this
this alright and you complete your sufficient
好了，您完成了足够的统计后，我们就可以得出
alright and you complete your sufficient statistics then we take derivatives with
statistics then we take derivatives with respect to a and gamma the game it looks
关于a和gamma游戏，它看起来与多元高斯相同
respect to a and gamma the game it looks identical to multivariate Gaussian you
identical to multivariate Gaussian you know and be obtained of a and gamma in
在m步中知道并获得a和gamma看起来像这样
know and be obtained of a and gamma in the m-step look like this really the
the m-step look like this really the only thing you need to compute again is
唯一需要再次计算的就是足够的统计数据了
only thing you need to compute again is the sufficient statistics okay
the sufficient statistics okay and the sufficient statistics for a and
而有关a和gamma的足够统计数据显然涉及了所有
and the sufficient statistics for a and gamma obviously they involve all the
gamma obviously they involve all the sufficient statistics overall little
足够的统计数据总体上左右偏左，所以您不知道
sufficient statistics overall little left right so you don't have you know in
left right so you don't have you know in this case all right well as suppose in
这种情况很好，就像在先前情况下对于初始状态所假设的一样
this case all right well as suppose in the previous case for the initial state
the previous case for the initial state you didn't have this
您没有这种关系，但是这里基本上没有
you didn't have this relations but here basically without the
relations but here basically without the summations that you need to make this to
您需要对此求和以类似方式进行求和
summations that you need to make this to go in similarly for this calculation of
go in similarly for this calculation of Sigma of Z and Sigma that they come in
他们又来了观测模型中的Z的Sigma和Sigma。费舍尔
Sigma of Z and Sigma that they come in the observation model again mr. Fisher's
the observation model again mr. Fisher's for distinct look like this okay and
看起来像这样好看，
实际上，您可以立即看到为什么我们造成了结局
the observation model again mr. Fisher's for distinct look like this okay and
actually you can see immediately why we had caused the end to be sort of to be
我们给NI取了什么名字忘了我
what's the name we gave to the N I forgot remind me
说这个词，但为此我累了，你知道我有道理，你知道
say the word but for that I'm tired you know I am justified you know with the
know I am justified you know with the world that's nice amenity responsibility
美好的世界便利责任还可以
world that's nice amenity responsibility okay
okay similarly the concept of the
同样，责任的概念，因为您了解自己
similarly the concept of the responsibility because you know you
responsibility because you know you completing C and if you take all the day
完成C，如果您整日都参加所有观察，但是您签署了
completing C and if you take all the day all the observations but you sign a
all the observations but you sign a posterior probability to each of them
他们知道的每个人的后验概率基本上可以估算出
posterior probability to each of them right you know estimate basically the
right you know estimate basically the only thing you need to do is when you're
唯一需要做的就是当您要去完成方程式时
only thing you need to do is when you're going and finish the equation when
going and finish the equation when you're going to compute this expectation
您将要计算这种期望，唯一可能的就是联合
you're going to compute this expectation the joint of likelihood the only thing
the joint of likelihood the only thing you have to do is write one put some log
你要做的就是在那里也写一个先验概率的日志
you have to do is write one put some log of the prior probability there as well
of the prior probability there as well and the rest is service it will change
其余的是服务，它将在导数之间进行任何更改以获得
and the rest is service it will change any between in the derivative to get
any between in the derivative to get some extra terms the doctors regular
一些额外的条款，基本上是医生的常规许可证，但可以获取地图
some extra terms the doctors regular license basically but getting the map
license basically but getting the map estimate is sort of trivial now again
估计现在又有点琐碎了，这认为它们看起来像是逗号类型的
estimate is sort of trivial now again this thinks they look like comma type of
this thinks they look like comma type of problems but you know as you can see you
问题，但您知道，因为您可以看到，您知道前者答应您知道有
problems but you know as you can see you know former promised you know there were
know former promised you know there were lots of progress on the spending habits
消费习惯方面有很多进步，您知道这是怎么回事
lots of progress on the spending habits how would this work you know they were
how would this work you know they were things done in the last 15-20 years so
在过去15到20年内完成的工作，因此这是一个很好的参考资料，其中包含
things done in the last 15-20 years so this a nice reference that contains this
this a nice reference that contains this sort of calculation
某种计算
好吧，我正在失去观众，今天发生的事情就像我在告诉
this a nice reference that contains this sort of calculation
okay I'm losing my audience what's happening today it's like I'm telling
好吧，我正在失去观众，今天发生的事情就像我在告诉
happening today it's like I'm telling that back for two minutes and then
回来两分钟，然后每个人都消失了，如果你尝试玩
that back for two minutes and then everybody's gone if you try to play with
everybody's gone if you try to play with this message passing and and references
此消息传递和和引用，我在这里没有它们，但如果您拒绝，
this message passing and and references I don't have them here but deny if you
I don't have them here but deny if you search you will find ways of doing this
搜索，您将找到执行此操作的方法，但可以说，您并非如此
search you will find ways of doing this but let's say that somehow you're not
but let's say that somehow you're not happy with messages that are gaussians
我对高斯语的消息感到满意我的意思是，我可以知道吗
happy with messages that are gaussians right I mean I can you know maybe you're
right I mean I can you know maybe you're nice model is not Gaussian maybe your
好的模型不是高斯模型，也许您的姓名缩写交易不是高斯模型，怎么办
nice model is not Gaussian maybe your initials trade is non Gaussian so how do
initials trade is non Gaussian so how do you use this equation let's say well
你用这个方程式，好吧，这是一个高斯混合，现在如果
you use this equation let's say well this is a Gaussian mixture okay now if
this is a Gaussian mixture okay now if business a Gaussian makes the right and
高斯人做正确的事，这里有时间，好吧xn
business a Gaussian makes the right and there's the time put here okay xn given
there's the time put here okay xn given Zn so you start with say with the
Zn，所以首先要说的是高斯z1的方法
Zn so you start with say with the methods of a z1 that is a Gaussian
methods of a z1 that is a Gaussian mixture then a of z2 will be also mixed
则z2的a也将与K平方分量基本混合
mixture then a of z2 will be also mixed with K square components basically it
with K square components basically it would be a Gaussian mixed with K cubed
将是高斯与K个立方分量混合而成的，所以基本上您知道
would be a Gaussian mixed with K cubed components so basically you know
components so basically you know identical dilatory explosion in
这些消息的组成部分相同的扩张式爆炸，因此唯一
identical dilatory explosion in components of these messages so the only
components of these messages so the only way that you can pursue sort of a non
您可以进行某种非高斯表示的方式可以提供额外的
way that you can pursue sort of a non Gaussian representation gives an extra
Gaussian representation gives an extra sphere would be to actually take
领域将实际上是用这种混合物吸引不同的听众
sphere would be to actually take different listeners with this mixtures
different listeners with this mixtures but before you update and you go to the
但在您更新之前，您将转到下一个投影回K的剪辑
but before you update and you go to the next clip projecting back to K
next clip projecting back to K components so your new combinations of K
组件，所以您的K平方组件的新组合，但随后您知道了
components so your new combinations of K square components but then you know
square components but then you know perhaps made this again with case J
也许用案例J组件再次做到这一点，
perhaps made this again with case J component and
手表记得麻省理工学院做过这种类型的手表的人
the wristwatch remember out of the group at MIT that had done this type of
at MIT that had done this type of calculations many 10 years course oh so
计算很多10年的过程哦，所以基本上是高斯人进行此更新
calculations many 10 years course oh so basically yes gaussians make this update
basically yes gaussians make this update progress analytical but you know if you
进行分析，但您知道是否要使用很长的时间
progress analytical but you know if you want to use anything that's long
want to use anything that's long Gaussian ignoring new territories and
高斯忽略新领域，您必须非常小心
Gaussian ignoring new territories and you have to be very careful how you do
you have to be very careful how you do okay
好吧，这并不意味着你做不到
okay it doesn't mean you cannot be done what
it doesn't mean you cannot be done what he means is not going to be easy to
他的意思是说要计算这个主题不容易
he means is not going to be easy to compute this topic is related with this
compute this topic is related with this type of exchange extensions when the
消息不是高斯时的交换分机类型您如何
type of exchange extensions when the messages are non Gaussian how do you
messages are non Gaussian how do you actually okay is there are other any
其实还可以，还有其他方法可以吗
actually okay is there are other any other methods okay
other methods okay and one of the methods that allows you
以及一种允许您发送不属于您的消息的方法之一
and one of the methods that allows you to do messages that they are non
to do messages that they are non Gaussian is to use a particle
高斯是使用痕迹的粒子表示，因此
Gaussian is to use a particle representation of the of the vestiges so
representation of the of the vestiges so you can figure out basically having the
您可以弄清楚基本上用顶部框表示的消息
you can figure out basically having the messages represented in terms of top box
messages represented in terms of top box alright and I know in the cola gave at
好吧，我知道在可乐中至少给了三四堂课
alright and I know in the cola gave at least three or four lectures of the
least three or four lectures of the topics are not quite sure how much you
主题不是很确定您将为我们讨论多少
topics are not quite sure how much you will be for us to discuss a lot of
will be for us to discuss a lot of details right somewhere try to spend
某处的细节尝试花费大约10分钟的时间，因为此地图
details right somewhere try to spend maybe 10 minutes okay because this maps
maybe 10 minutes okay because this maps are extremely powerful like for example
非常强大，例如在解决一切问题的机器人技术方面
are extremely powerful like for example in robotics in tackling everything is
in robotics in tackling everything is using particle methods because those
使用粒子方法，因为那些发射时间长的高斯是
using particle methods because those emissions long work gaussians are the
emissions long work gaussians are the wrong approach equation so the only way
错误的进近方程式，因此唯一的出路是时间逼近法或
wrong approach equation so the only way out is time approximation method or
out is time approximation method or using this part of things okay
好好利用这部分内容，现在我知道了第十堂课-
using this part of things okay now I know about the 10th of the class -
now I know about the 10th of the class - good luck with my you know attending my
祝你好运，我知道你在洞里参加我的演讲
good luck with my you know attending my lectures in the hole
lectures in the hole but I also test that the remember
但我也测试过，记得没事
but I also test that the remember nothing okay
nothing okay right you sick they remember absolutely
对，你生病了，他们绝对不记得任何东西，所以让我，所以我不会
right you sick they remember absolutely nothing so let me so I'm not going to
nothing so let me so I'm not going to let me jump okay
让我跳好吧，对不起，我不会告诉你
let me jump okay sorry I'm not going to tell you
sorry I'm not going to tell you everything
一切
好吧，我来讨论一下这种预测和状态更新
sorry I'm not going to tell you everything
alright so me discuss sort of this prediction and update of the state that
好吧，我来讨论一下这种预测和状态更新
prediction and update of the state that we use basically for the Kalman filter
我们基本上将以前的讲座中的卡尔曼滤波器方程式用于
we use basically for the Kalman filter equations of the previous lectures and
equations of the previous lectures and when I show here is rather than of
当我在这里展示时，而不是在他们认为当时建立一种状态
when I show here is rather than of making one state at the time they think
making one state at the time they think so in this case from the Stefan versus
因此，在这种情况下，根据Stefan与预测，我得到的数据是1到n的负值
so in this case from the Stefan versus prediction I have data from 1 to n minus
prediction I have data from 1 to n minus 1 all right
1好的，我正在更新所有状态
1 all right and I'm updating all the states
and I'm updating all the states including our state n and the addition
包括我们的状态n以及预测步骤的添加是
including our state n and the addition of the prediction step is the end of
of the prediction step is the end of this distribution at the joint of Z's
在给定X 1 n减1的情况下，Z的连接处从1到N减1的分布
this distribution at the joint of Z's from 1 to N minus 1 given X 1 n minus 1
from 1 to N minus 1 given X 1 n minus 1 so this prediction one step ahead only
因此，这一预测仅向前迈进了一段时期，
so this prediction one step ahead only involves lives of these dynamics the
involves lives of these dynamics the probability of Zn given Zn minus 1 okay
给定Zn减去1好的Zn的概率，因此再次用于过滤a
probability of Zn given Zn minus 1 okay right so again in for the filtering a
right so again in for the filtering a question the prediction step involving
对此处涉及变量的预测步骤提出质疑，只是因为我
question the prediction step involving the variables here here just because I
the variables here here just because I company's equations for much more
公司方程式，用于更通用的计算类型I
company's equations for much more general sort of type of calculations I
general sort of type of calculations I demonstrate this when we keep the
当我们保持所有这些变量的后验确定时，证明这一点
demonstrate this when we keep the posterior of all of these variables ok
posterior of all of these variables ok so this is the prediction for one step
所以这是对我们已经看到的，以及随着我们前进的一步的预测
so this is the prediction for one step ahead that we have seen and and as we
ahead that we have seen and and as we discussed even today if you want now if
甚至在今天讨论过，如果您现在想要，如果您观察到想要的话
discussed even today if you want now if you observe want you
you observe want you the point xn and you want to update the
xn点，您想更新所有Z的n到n的正则
the point xn and you want to update the prospero of all the Z's up to n then
prospero of all the Z's up to n then definitely what you need to do is take
当然，您需要做的就是将此分布乘以
definitely what you need to do is take this distribution multiplied with the
this distribution multiplied with the observation model xn given Zn so in a
观测模型xn给定了Zn，所以在一个粒子中会存在金属，因此，如果您知道
observation model xn given Zn so in a particle that metals so if you you know
particle that metals so if you you know make all of this delusion then you get
进行所有这些妄想，然后就可以得到这些过滤器方程式，因为
make all of this delusion then you get that these filter equations ok because
that these filter equations ok because here I don't have all my observations on
在这里，我没有对每个子项目的所有观察来帮助确定，所以您可以获得颜色
here I don't have all my observations on each sub to help ok so you get the color
each sub to help ok so you get the color of entry questions for this so the idea
的入门问题，所以这个粒子水平的想法正在问
of entry questions for this so the idea of this particle levels are asking
of this particle levels are asking informant in time to represent these
线人及时用样本来代表这些分布而没有
informant in time to represent these distributions with samples without
distributions with samples without detection
确定还可以，并且以某种方式获得另一种理解
detection ok and somehow another one understanding
ok and somehow another one understanding the distributions as you go from one
从一步到另一步的分布基本上是
the distributions as you go from one step to another are provide basically
step to another are provide basically the the waves of this Delta functions as
当您从n减1到n右移时，此Delta的波浪会起作用
the the waves of this Delta functions as you go from n minus 1 to n right
you go from n minus 1 to n right so the idea here is that you have Delta
所以这里的想法是您有Delta函数，但是我们将对它们进行一些分类
so the idea here is that you have Delta functions but in shall we do class some
functions but in shall we do class some of the Cardinal the weight is the same
红衣主教的体重是相同的，所以我们将有加权的样本
of the Cardinal the weight is the same so we're going to have weighted samples
so we're going to have weighted samples to express these distributions and if
表达这些分布，如果您是我，则表示这些分布
to express these distributions and if your I these distributions in terms of
your I these distributions in terms of samples you can actually in principle
您实际上可以在原则上表示任何种类的分布的样本
samples you can actually in principle represent any sort of distributions can
represent any sort of distributions can be anything all right
没关系，任何事情都是非常分散的
be anything all right anything that the distribution is very
anything that the distribution is very complex you will need more samples but
复杂，您将需要更多样本，但是这里的想法是，如果您
complex you will need more samples but this ideas here it comes out that if you
this ideas here it comes out that if you take the samples and somehow you update
采取示例，以某种方式进行更新，是迈向另一步的方法
take the samples and somehow you update are ways to one step to another the
are ways to one step to another the algoriphagus the complexity that depends
食藻的复杂性取决于样品的面积或数量
algoriphagus the complexity that depends the area or the number of the samples
the area or the number of the samples not on the little n so in principle you
不是在小n上，所以原则上您可以永远这样做，您可以
not on the little n so in principle you can keep doing this forever you can
can keep doing this forever you can control us
控制我们从2到
control us distribution from time while 2 to
distribution from time while 2 to infinity even though there would be the
即使存在慷慨的问题以及所有这些事情
infinity even though there would be the generous issues and all the things that
generous issues and all the things that we have no time to discuss ok give you
我们没有时间讨论好了，基本上给你，我实际上我要走了
we have no time to discuss ok give you basically I'm actually I'm going to go
basically I'm actually I'm going to go directly on the picture okay since we
直接在图片上好吧，因为我们是Vista，所以我们在这里是山
directly on the picture okay since we Vista so so we have here is the mountain
Vista so so we have here is the mountain the define them and we know the temple
定义它们，我们知道分布中的神殿，我写了幽灵
the define them and we know the temple in distribution and I write the specter
in distribution and I write the specter in distribution in terms of this
在此粒子服务事件的分布方面，功能
in distribution in terms of this particle service event the functions
particle service event the functions that are you know sentient basically on
你知道这部分基本上是有感觉的，这是Z n好吧的资本，
that are you know sentient basically on this part it was capital of Z n okay and
this part it was capital of Z n okay and this are wage okay in the way it's
这是可以的，实际上我代表的是
this are wage okay in the way it's actually when I represent this are the
actually when I represent this are the particles a different location and to
粒子在不同的位置，并指出更大的方向
particles a different location and to indicate which way it's a bigger
indicate which way it's a bigger basically it's a bigger okay so to be
基本上，这是一个更大的问题，这样才能使这些粒子向前移动并
basically it's a bigger okay so to be able to move forward this particles and
able to move forward this particles and compute the filtering distribution time
计算过滤分布时间n加1您记得我需要做两个
compute the filtering distribution time n plus 1 you remember I need to do two
n plus 1 you remember I need to do two things first I need to move most fair
首先，我需要用这种动力学模型进行最公平的选择，然后
things first I need to move most fair which with this dynamical model and then
which with this dynamical model and then I need to apply the observation the
我需要在给定Z的情况下应用观察X的发射概率P
I need to apply the observation the emission probabilities P of X given Z so
emission probabilities P of X given Z so the variability is assuming that you
可变性假设您具有此粒子分布，如果您
the variability is assuming that you have this particle distribution if you
have this particle distribution if you take this update equations other hands
好吧，如果您应用了
take this update equations other hands before alright and if you apply the
before alright and if you apply the levity update equation somewhere I have
某处的高度更新方程我有一个更新方程这是什么
levity update equation somewhere I have an update equation what is it here this
an update equation what is it here this is the prediction for one step ahead the
是向前迈出一步的预测唯一要做的就是休息
is the prediction for one step ahead the only thing you have to do is take rest
only thing you have to do is take rest approach in terms of particles and then
接近粒子，然后将其与动力学模型相乘
approach in terms of particles and then multiply this with the dynamical model
multiply this with the dynamical model of P of Z L given Zn minus 1 so
ZL的P的给定为Zn减去1，所以基本上这是我在这里所做的
of P of Z L given Zn minus 1 so basically this is what I have done here
basically this is what I have done here all right I compute
好吧，我计算CN的后验加一个仍然给定的
all right I compute the posterior of CN plus one still given
the posterior of CN plus one still given heaven with only the date of the time
天堂，只有时间的男人
heaven with only the date of the time man
man so this one required this posterior of
因此，这需要CN的后验，并在末尾给定1，然后
so this one required this posterior of CN plus 1 given at the end and then
CN plus 1 given at the end and then because you have these Delta functions
因为您有这些Delta函数，我们必须计算这个后验
because you have these Delta functions this posterior we have to be calculated
this posterior we have to be calculated given its particle I don't know if you
给定它的粒子，我不知道你是否能看到你真正得到的东西
given its particle I don't know if you can see what you actually get through
can see what you actually get through there is terms of a Gaussian mixture
有高斯混合项
正确，您可以得到高斯x2分布，因为我们没有
can see what you actually get through there is terms of a Gaussian mixture
right you get the Gaussian x2 distribution okay and because we don't
正确，您可以得到高斯x2分布，因为我们没有
distribution okay and because we don't like thousand extras what you can do is
像上千个临时演员一样，你可以做的是，你可以理解所有这一切
like thousand extras what you can do is you can understand all this all right
you can understand all this all right you can example this and if your sample
您可以举这个例子，如果您的样本显示所有新样本
you can example this and if your sample is show that all the new samples
is show that all the new samples basically have equal weight the way you
基本上拥有与蒙特卡洛相同的重量，这点
basically have equal weight the way you do with Monte Carlo and this little
do with Monte Carlo and this little squares here little circles for equal
正方形，此处为新样本的等半径基准周期的小圆圈
squares here little circles for equal radius base period of the new samples
radius base period of the new samples that give you this one step ahead
可以让您提前这一步预测分配，好吧，那么我
that give you this one step ahead predicted distribution okay so then I
predicted distribution okay so then I took my filtering distribution at time N
在时间N进行了过滤分布，现在我提前了一步
took my filtering distribution at time N and I now do one step ahead prediction
and I now do one step ahead prediction with recently and I get this little star
最近，我收到了这个小星星的消息，剩下的实际上是
with recently and I get this little star post ok and what remains is to actually
post ok and what remains is to actually multiply this distribution with the
将该分布与观察模型相乘，该观察模型为给定的X的P
multiply this distribution with the observation model which is P of X given
observation model which is P of X given Z and if you do that because you have
Z，如果您这样做，是因为您具有此Delta函数，则新
Z and if you do that because you have this Delta functions the new
this Delta functions the new distribution will be basically the
分布基本上就是这些粒子给定的效果
distribution will be basically the effects given each of these particles
effects given each of these particles times this Delta function but you
将这个Delta函数乘以倍数，但是您可以在那里计算它，以便可以看到新的
times this Delta function but you compute it there so you can see the new
compute it there so you can see the new filter in this position the location of
过滤器在此位置的位置不变，但
filter in this position the location of the part of this hasn't changed but the
the part of this hasn't changed but the waste have changed because the weights
浪费已经改变，因为现在的重量是由观测者决定的
waste have changed because the weights now are dictated by the observational
now are dictated by the observational model of P of X given C
给定C的X的P的模型
我知道那里有太多东西，但我需要告诉你
now are dictated by the observational model of P of X given C
I know there is too much there to get but I need to tell you about this
我知道那里有太多东西，但我需要告诉你
but I need to tell you about this because some of these methods are the
因为其中一些方法是实际使用的方法
because some of these methods are the methods that are used in practice
methods that are used in practice this is how we're gonna implement the
这就是我们要实施培训师的方式
this is how we're gonna implement the trainer
trainer Gaussian models maybe even a linear
高斯模型甚至可以是线性模型，也可以是非高斯噪声的单位
Gaussian models maybe even a linear models or unity of non Gaussian noise
models or unity of non Gaussian noise you know this meant was work and they
您知道这意味着工作，它们是用于
you know this meant was work and they are sort of the standard methods for
are sort of the standard methods for implementing lists of data questions in
在很多领域实施数据问题清单
implementing lists of data questions in many areas all right
many areas all right many are okay I'm actually with the bad
许多人还好，我实际上是出于我承诺要给我的不愉快的理由
many are okay I'm actually with the bad reasons I have committed to give I don't
reasons I have committed to give I don't know how many lectures this summer in
知道今年夏天在另一所大学上有多少次讲座
know how many lectures this summer in another university on the top of this
another university on the top of this type of metals so if you are interested
金属的类型，因此，如果您有兴趣，我会尝试准备一些具体的
type of metals so if you are interested I will try to sort of prepare specific
I will try to sort of prepare specific notes from scotts basically for this
斯科特的笔记基本上是关于方法的这一部分的，也许是通过
notes from scotts basically for this part of into methods maybe by by
part of into methods maybe by by mid-june or so okay so what a wise you
中旬左右还可以，所以您可以明智地看一下课程中的笔记
mid-june or so okay so what a wise you can look at the notes from the course
can look at the notes from the course last semester that contains more
上学期，其中包含更多信息，对此有任何疑问，请访问
last semester that contains more information any questions to this at
information any questions to this at least in spirit what they are I mean the
至少从精神上讲，我的意思是整个想法是我代表
least in spirit what they are I mean the whole idea is I represent the
whole idea is I represent the distributions the splintering
根据样本权分配分散的分布
distributions the splintering distributions in terms of samples right
distributions in terms of samples right and a distribution in terms of samples
就样本而言，分布就是一堆Delta函数
and a distribution in terms of samples is a bunch of Delta functions all right
is a bunch of Delta functions all right if you just need these are depending how
如果您只需要这些，则取决于我们如何进行采样以了解
if you just need these are depending how we do the sampling to know if the
we do the sampling to know if the weights are equal or they are different
权重相等或不同，所以在这种情况下，您可以从
weights are equal or they are different okay and so in this case you start with
okay and so in this case you start with so when we see some of the start with
因此，当我们看到某些起点比其他起点更大时，权重会有所不同
so when we see some of the start with bigger than others the weights different
bigger than others the weights different but if you sample from this you notice
但是，如果您从中采样，您会发现像这样的采样随着您的使用而退化
but if you sample from this you notice like this sample that has degrade as you
like this sample that has degrade as you sample it gives you two children by just
样本仅凭主意就给了您两个孩子，因为您不必担心
sample it gives you two children by just the idea because there's no worry okay
the idea because there's no worry okay but it's not the new samples all of them
但这不是新样本，现在所有样本都具有相同的方式，然后是
but it's not the new samples all of them have now equal way okay and then this is
have now equal way okay and then this is your observation model so obviously
您的观察模型，很明显，这些样本例如在这里，当我们
your observation model so obviously these samples for example here when we
these samples for example here when we passed and prove this observation model
通过并证明了这个观察模型我们有更大的权重，在这里我们再次
passed and prove this observation model we have bigger weight and again here we
we have bigger weight and again here we have bigger weights of they're small and
重量较大，所以重量较小，所以这是一种非常有效的方法
have bigger weights of they're small and so this is sort of a very powerful way
so this is sort of a very powerful way to do something to do small thing to
做某事做小事，有很多不同类型的
to do something to do small thing to there are lots of different type of
there are lots of different type of things and then the standard levels as I
事物，然后是我在任何形式的机器人技术中所说的标准水平
things and then the standard levels as I said in robotics in in any sort of
said in robotics in in any sort of dynamical problems not on your body
动态问题，不会在您的身体上碰到任何东西
dynamical problems not on your body touching anything all right
touching anything all right we have a few minutes left so let me
我们还有几分钟的时间，所以让我太平洋告诉您如何完成此操作
we have a few minutes left so let me Pacific how show you can finish this
Pacific how show you can finish this topic how you extend this ideas when the
主题当模型不是线性时如何扩展这些想法，所以我们
topic how you extend this ideas when the model is not linear all right so so we
model is not linear all right so so we had two linear models right both the
有两个线性模型，它们的动力学都正确，因为您知道的Z
had two linear models right both the dynamics it was for the Z you know
dynamics it was for the Z you know remember Z n equal a Z n minus 1 plus
记住Z n等于Z n减去1再加上噪声
remember Z n equal a Z n minus 1 plus noise let's say that the relation is not
noise let's say that the relation is not linear then we basically have the N
线性的，那么我们基本上让N减1到某个线性函数f
linear then we basically have the N minus 1 goes to some linear function f
minus 1 goes to some linear function f of X to give me to give me Z n okay you
X的给我给我的Z n好吧，您可以这样做，而不是
of X to give me to give me Z n okay you can do this you know in in instead of
can do this you know in in instead of the matrix a or you can have something
矩阵a或您可以有类似的表示噪声的方法，但是
the matrix a or you can have something like that to represent noise okay but
like that to represent noise okay but the bottom line is the relation we have
底线是我们在n减去1和n全部之间的变量之间的关系
the bottom line is the relation we have between variables at n minus 1 and n all
between variables at n minus 1 and n all between the state and the observations
在给定的时间内，状态和观察值之间存在耦合关系
between the state and the observations in the given time they're coupled to
in the given time they're coupled to some nonlinear function and so we need
一些非线性函数，所以我们需要找到一些方法来处理它
some nonlinear function and so we need to find some way to deal with it
就颗粒而言，当我说我们
in terms of particles you know that's not an issue right so well when I say we
not an issue right so well when I say we need to find some way to deal with this
需要找到一些方法来解决这个问题，我们是否真的可以尝试碳
need to find some way to deal with this can we actually want to try the carbon
can we actually want to try the carbon filter equations to do that okay and the
过滤方程式就可以了，当然答案是可以
filter equations to do that okay and the answer of course is yes you can
answer of course is yes you can so yes then this is the trivial model so
所以是的，那么这是微不足道的模型，所以说动力学是由
so yes then this is the trivial model so let's say the the dynamics are given by
let's say the the dynamics are given by this function G okay and the observation
可以，这个函数和另一个非线性函数的观测模型
this function G okay and the observation model by another nonlinear function
model by another nonlinear function eight okay so the phonology is called
八行，所以语音学被称为扩展卡尔曼滤波器，它是
eight okay so the phonology is called the extended Kalman filter and it's
the extended Kalman filter and it's nothing else but linearization of GNH
除了GNH的线性化和先前的状态估计之外
nothing else but linearization of GNH and among the previous state estimates
and among the previous state estimates using basically a Taylor series
基本上使用泰勒级数展开式
using basically a Taylor series expansion
expansion okay and actually there are versions of
好的，实际上，您可以先在此表格的某些版本上使用
okay and actually there are versions of this form you can use first on the
this form you can use first on the Taylor expansion and also a second of
泰勒展开式和佩德罗展开式的二分之一，您可以做任何事情
Taylor expansion and also a second of the Pedro expansion you can do anything
the Pedro expansion you can do anything you want to the against once you
一旦您估计了这一点，您就想反对
you want to the against once you approximate this and you you know if you
approximate this and you you know if you use the Taylor series expansion will
使用泰勒级数展开式将给您一些线性项，即3-1
use the Taylor series expansion will give you sort of a linear term is a 3-1
give you sort of a linear term is a 3-1 or a near term intensity and so would
或近期强度，所以您可以将导数乘以90减去
or a near term intensity and so would you sort of a derivative times 90 minus
you sort of a derivative times 90 minus 1 and if you approximate the derivative
1，如果您近似先前状态的导数，则公共
1 and if you approximate the derivative of the previous state then the common
of the previous state then the common equation so really it's super fancy bra
方程式，所以它真的是超级花式胸罩，我认为那里真的什么也没有
equation so really it's super fancy bra there is really nothing there I think
there is really nothing there I think the equations are sort of in your eyes
这些方程式就在您的眼中，然后仅将其剪切并粘贴
the equations are sort of in your eyes and then cut and paste from the only
and then cut and paste from the only questions from the new questions but let
新问题中的问题，但让我以图形方式向您展示什么想法
questions from the new questions but let me show you graphically what the idea
me show you graphically what the idea here is so remember we have
记住这里，我们有一些运行某些功能的功能
here is so remember we have as some function some running a function
as some function some running a function G of X all right so if X is a Gaussian
X的G可以，所以如果X是高斯，则想法是在计算时
G of X all right so if X is a Gaussian the idea is when you compute let's say
the idea is when you compute let's say which Montecarlo y equals G of X you
蒙特卡洛y等于X的G您没有得到高斯，您得到了真实的
which Montecarlo y equals G of X you don't get a Gaussian you get a real
don't get a Gaussian you get a real distribution of usage here so this
此处的使用情况分布，因此该双峰分布还可以，
distribution of usage here so this bimodal distribution okay so the
bimodal distribution okay so the question is not really neat to do when
当我们采用高斯并应用此问题时，问题并不是真的很整洁
question is not really neat to do when we take a Gaussian and we apply this
we take a Gaussian and we apply this mapping to effects to get the Gaussian
映射到效果以获得高斯权，因此扩展了这个想法
mapping to effects to get the Gaussian right and so the idea for this extended
right and so the idea for this extended color filter is to do linearization in
彩色滤光片是在X ok模式下进行线性化，然后基本上
color filter is to do linearization in the mode of X ok and then basically
the mode of X ok and then basically alright so this is the approximation we
好吧，这就是近似值，我们可以做得很好，然后我们通过
alright so this is the approximation we do all right and then we pass the
do all right and then we pass the probability we passed this line through
我们通过X的P的概率通过这条线的概率，这将
probability we passed this line through the probability of P of X and that will
the probability of P of X and that will give me this dotted Gaussian which is
给我这个点缀的高斯曲线，它扩展了我们的高斯曲线领域，
give me this dotted Gaussian which is the expanding our field of Gaussian that
the expanding our field of Gaussian that has a mean basically that is given by
基本上有一个平均值，就是这个值给定的，所以
has a mean basically that is given by this value here okay so how does the
this value here okay so how does the linearization look like so for example
线性化看起来像这样，例如这是您的观测顺序
linearization look like so for example this is the observation order your
this is the observation order your interest first on the table since the
兴趣首先放在桌子上，因为这是值的问题，所以我们有H
interest first on the table since the question this is the value so we had H
question this is the value so we had H here right so we is the value is
在这里正确，所以我们是根据先前的平均值计算得出的值，如果
here right so we is the value is computed at the previous mean okay if
computed at the previous mean okay if you remember this notation which is near
您还记得这种表示法接近50减1是什么的主要
you remember this notation which is near 50 minus 1 is the main of what
50 minus 1 is the main of what distribution then this is the
分布，那么这是观察上正确的，那么什么是TT
distribution then this is the observationally right so what is mere TT
observationally right so what is mere TT minus 1
负1
3-1之后通过此收集了多少数据，所以这是
observationally right so what is mere TT minus 1
how many data have collected through this after 3-1 so this is the main of
3-1之后通过此收集了多少数据，所以这是
this after 3-1 so this is the main of the one step ahead prolific distribution
通过使用
the one step ahead prolific distribution okay some approximating age using the
okay some approximating age using the mean plus the derivative at the same
均值加上导数在同一位置乘以该误差
mean plus the derivative at the same location times the error of this one
location times the error of this one have I had in prediction the other if
如果您从观察Y键看，我是否已经预测过另一个
have I had in prediction the other if you look from the observation Y key okay
you look from the observation Y key okay I don't know why it is white you know
我不知道为什么白色是您知道的文字，但无论如何都会出现
I don't know why it is white you know text but anyways coming forward from
text but anyways coming forward from here of their give us different
他们给我们提供了不同的方程式，所以基本上他们告诉我们
here of their give us different equations so so basically they tell us
equations so so basically they tell us this expansion here around the mean of
这种扩展是围绕一只手的平均值向前迈出一步的
this expansion here around the mean of the one hand one step ahead predictive
the one hand one step ahead predictive distribution okay another place there's
分布好，另一个地方，绝对没有什么不同
distribution okay another place there's absolutely nothing different from what
absolutely nothing different from what we had before if you remember the linear
我们以前有过，如果您还记得进行整合的线性模型，她会
we had before if you remember the linear model for coming up integration she goes
model for coming up integration she goes the Gaussian of YT given let's say what
给出的YT的高斯让我们说我们在这里有什么指标
the Gaussian of YT given let's say what was the metrics that we have here you
was the metrics that we have here you see sometimes right p plus some constant
有时看到正确的p加一些常数，所以常数是这个减去这次
see sometimes right p plus some constant so the constant is this minus this times
so the constant is this minus this times that okay and of course here I'm
没关系，当然我在这里想的是最吵的高斯音
that okay and of course here I'm thinking that the noisiest Gaussian okay
thinking that the noisiest Gaussian okay if the noisiest Gaussian is not Gaussian
如果最吵闹的高斯人不是高斯人，那么你就必须把东西结合起来
if the noisiest Gaussian is not Gaussian basically you have to incorporate things
basically you have to incorporate things in a slightly different form okay
形式略有不同，好吧，
in a slightly different form okay and you know same thing for the
and you know same thing for the evolution of the of the dynamics let's
动力学的演变让我们不用担心你，好学生
evolution of the of the dynamics let's not bother about you all right students
not bother about you all right students really move it on the previous slide so
确实在上一张幻灯片上移动它，所以基本上您可以采用线性泰勒级数
really move it on the previous slide so basically you take linear Taylor series
basically you take linear Taylor series expansion around these the previous
前一天晚上围绕这些扩展的三个阶段的主要内容
expansion around these the previous night the main of the three stage which
night the main of the three stage which is near t minus one and this is the
接近t减一，这又是错误乘以这个雅可比行列式
is near t minus one and this is the error again times this Jacobian there
error again times this Jacobian there but there's a gradient position Z with
但相对于ZI有一个倾斜位置Z表示您一旦知道
but there's a gradient position Z with respect to Z I mean you know once you do
respect to Z I mean you know once you do this if you look at your genetic type of
如果您查看简单方程式的遗传类型，是否将其剪切并粘贴
this if you look at your genetic type of simple equations did you cut and paste
simple equations did you cut and paste on solvers
在求解器上更新，这是您的矩阵xy
on solvers updating that this is your matrix x y
updating that this is your matrix x y this is the constant and the rest is
这是常数，其余的非常有用，如果您知道的话
this is the constant and the rest is very useful okay and if anyone you know
very useful okay and if anyone you know of notation basically you know if you do
表示法的基本原理是，您知道如果执行此线性化处理，则可以得到各种
of notation basically you know if you do this linearization you can get various
this linearization you can get various different versions of this extended
扩展卡尔曼滤波器的不同版本，包括所谓的
different versions of this extended Kalman filter including what's called
Kalman filter including what's called its innovative dkf if anybody is
它的创新性dkf如果有人感兴趣，我可以给你阅读
its innovative dkf if anybody is interested I can give you to read a very
interested I can give you to read a very nice book by a stonker that I promise
stonker的一本好书，我保证您可以在不到三分钟的时间内阅读完
nice book by a stonker that I promise you you can read it in less than three
you you can read it in less than three hours okay and he has a computer program
几个小时还可以，他有一个计算机程序，它中没有任何内容
hours okay and he has a computer program that comes with it has nothing in the
that comes with it has nothing in the conditional probability graphical models
条件概率图形模型，但一切都从零开始，包括
conditional probability graphical models but is everything from zero including
but is everything from zero including applications to the most complex sort of
应用程序以最复杂的方式完成某种本质
applications to the most complex sort of way for doing some sort of essence of
way for doing some sort of essence of karma filter if you'll read the book in
如果您会在三小时零一分钟内读完这本书，则将其设为
karma filter if you'll read the book in three hours and a minute
three hours and a minute so if anybody's interested I think it's
因此，如果有人感兴趣，我认为它可以在线访问，并且您知道访问权限
so if anybody's interested I think it's online that okay and if you know access
online that okay and if you know access but you can actually reach this Christus
但实际上，您可以在此之前两到三年到达Christus
but you can actually reach this Christus that is two or three years before this
that is two or three years before this book okay
书还好，所以你可以看看那些东西只有六个
book okay so you can look at those things just six
so you can look at those things just six minutes finis right another algorithm is
分钟finis另一个算法是表格的不确定性列
minutes finis right another algorithm is the uncertainty column of the table to
the uncertainty column of the table to do TRAI and the idea here is that it is
做TRAI，这里的想法是更容易近似高斯运行
do TRAI and the idea here is that it is easier to approximate the Gaussian run
easier to approximate the Gaussian run the log to approximate the function
该日志近似函数，因此实际上是线性粘贴
the log to approximate the function so actually one to linear paste the
so actually one to linear paste the function you tried actually to
您实际上尝试近似一些数据以适合
function you tried actually to approximate some data to fit the
approximate some data to fit the Gaussian so basically don't manipulate
高斯，因此基本上不操纵试图使数据适合的函数
Gaussian so basically don't manipulate the function trying to make data to fit
the function trying to make data to fit in some Gaussian point okay and how do
在一些高斯点好吧，你怎么做到的
in some Gaussian point okay and how do you do this
you do this so here's the idea if the ocean all
所以这是一个想法，如果海洋没事，这是没有气味的
so here's the idea if the ocean all right this is this is the unscented
right this is this is the unscented transport basically that you have to use
基本上，如果您有适合的发行版，则必须使用
transport basically that you have to use if you have some distribution that fits
if you have some distribution that fits in the Gaussian and you want to pass
在高斯中，您要将其传递给形式为y等于f的映射
in the Gaussian and you want to pass this to a mapping of the form y equal f
this to a mapping of the form y equal f of X right F is a nonlinear function
X右F是一个非线性函数，您需要做的是
of X right F is a nonlinear function which you need to do is you need to
which you need to do is you need to compute what is called Sigma points and
计算所谓的Sigma点，这些基本上就是您所需要的常数
compute what is called Sigma points and these are constants basically that you
these are constants basically that you can optimize all right these are the
可以优化所有这些是Sigma矩阵的列
can optimize all right these are the columns of the Sigma matrix this is the
columns of the Sigma matrix this is the mean of this G of X so you calculate the
X的G的均值，所以您计算Sigma森林而永远无法做到这一点
mean of this G of X so you calculate the Sigma forest and never can do this
Sigma forest and never can do this you Paskus this Sigma points through the
您使Paskus这个Sigma指向函数f，然后拟合该数据
you Paskus this Sigma points through the function f and then you fit this data
function f and then you fit this data wise to now sir that's all
明智的做法是，先生，再说一次，与此功能相关的钱f
wise to now sir that's all so again money relating this function f
so again money relating this function f to give you a linear equation that will
给你一个线性方程，这将导致你的衣服达到高斯
to give you a linear equation that will lead to a Gaussian with the dress you
lead to a Gaussian with the dress you introduced this Sigma points okay
介绍这个西格玛点好吧，在这种情况下，他们必须D加1
introduced this Sigma points okay and in this case they have to D plus 1
and in this case they have to D plus 1 points you pass this through the
点，您可以通过函数f进行传递，然后通过
points you pass this through the function f and then in through the
function f and then in through the Gaussian so obviously in our case we
高斯很明显，在我们的情况下，我们必须做两次，而你要做
Gaussian so obviously in our case we have to do this twice you have to do
have to do this twice you have to do this for the the dynamical model and we
这是针对动力学模型的，对于观察性模型，我们必须这样做
this for the the dynamical model and we have to do this for the observational
have to do this for the observational model and effectively if so if you pass
建模并且有效，如果是这样的话，如果您通过函数传递此参数并且想要
model and effectively if so if you pass this through the function and you want
this through the function and you want to compute the mean and the variance
计算平均值和方差，这是一般响应，可以
to compute the mean and the variance this the general response okay this
this the general response okay this looks very much like sample mean the
看起来非常像样本，这意味着样本方差是这里唯一的区别
looks very much like sample mean the sample variance the only difference here
sample variance the only difference here is because these points were selected in
是因为以最佳方式选择了这些点的权重
is because these points were selected in the some optimal way their weights would
the some optimal way their weights would not be equal so you know the weights
不相等，所以您知道它们的权重必须根据
not be equal so you know the weights they have to be calculated depending on
they have to be calculated depending on the parameters that you use in the
如果您尝试在不确定运输中使用的参数
the parameters that you use in the uncertain transport if you try to do
uncertain transport if you try to do this in one day in case you get inspired
一天之内，以防万一您被启发，这使您想起三个
this in one day in case you get inspired that this reminds you anything the three
that this reminds you anything the three points for example that you're going to
例如，要使用的点在一次处理中被赋予高斯
points for example that you're going to use is given Gaussian in one deal with
use is given Gaussian in one deal with mu nu minus square root of 3 times Sigma
mu nu减去3倍Sigma的平方根和mu plus平方根3倍Sigma的根
mu nu minus square root of 3 times Sigma and mu plus square root of 3 times Sigma
and mu plus square root of 3 times Sigma and the algorithm is again sort of the
算法还是第一步，我们需要预测一个
and the algorithm is again sort of the first step is we need to predict the one
first step is we need to predict the one hand of step so to compute the filtering
步骤的第一步，以便再次计算过滤分布
hand of step so to compute the filtering distribution again right you first have
distribution again right you first have to go one step ahead with observations
只有在t减去1好的情况下才向前进行观察，所以要这样做
to go one step ahead with observations only after t minus 1 okay so to do this
only after t minus 1 okay so to do this what we have to do is pass the previous
我们要做的是通过先前的高斯分布
what we have to do is pass the previous Gaussian distribution the Gaussian
Gaussian distribution the Gaussian approximation we had for the filter and
我们对CP的滤波和分布减去1的近似值
approximation we had for the filter and distribution of CP minus 1 so what you
distribution of CP minus 1 so what you need to this first this through the
首先需要通过定义运动学的函数G
need to this first this through the function G that defines the kinematic
function G that defines the kinematic model right the dynamical model G so
正确的动力学模型G基本上是从这种下降开始的
model right the dynamical model G so basically start with this decline the
basically start with this decline the Sigma points and then pass them to G and
Sigma点，然后将它们传递给G，然后计算方差的平均值
Sigma points and then pass them to G and then to compute the mean of the variance
then to compute the mean of the variance of that you weight them appropriately
其中，您可以使用
of that you weight them appropriately using the standard formulas from the
using the standard formulas from the insensitive small and you get the mean
麻木不仁的小，您就可以得到波动率的平均值，并且
insensitive small and you get the mean of the volatility like that and
of the volatility like that and eventually to genetic impedance of this
最终成为该观察模型的遗传阻抗，但是是非线性的
eventually to genetic impedance of this observation model but is nonlinear okay
observation model but is nonlinear okay so so what you need to miss you need to
因此，您需要错过的事情需要传递Sigma T的强大功能
so so what you need to miss you need to pass the power of Sigma T that we
pass the power of Sigma T that we completed the previous step there is the
完成了上一步，伦敦观察就好了，所以这就是
completed the previous step there is the observation London okay so this is what
observation London okay so this is what you get okay and then eventually you are
你会好起来的，然后最终你将要拥有一种
you get okay and then eventually you are going to have this is sort of a
going to have this is sort of a likelihood and this is sort of like a
可能性，这有点像入门，所以您需要做
likelihood and this is sort of like a primer so you're going to need to do the
primer so you're going to need to do the 2013 distribution you will need to use
您需要使用贝叶斯规则和计算概率的2013年分布
2013 distribution you will need to use Bayes rule and compute the probability
Bayes rule and compute the probability of Z given Y so if you have nice and and
的Z给定Y，所以如果您有好感，并且如果您有Z的P，那么它们基本上是
of Z given Y so if you have nice and and if you have P of Z they're basically
if you have P of Z they're basically just Vegas truth directly it can give
只是拉斯维加斯真相，它可以为您提供过滤分布，所以这
just Vegas truth directly it can give you the filtering distribution so this
you the filtering distribution so this is just from the formulas for Gaussian
只是从高斯线性模型的公式中注意到这一点而已
is just from the formulas for Gaussian linear models by noting specific this
linear models by noting specific this once alpha qkf algorithm is basically
一旦alpha qkf算法基本上很聪明，另一种推理就是
once alpha qkf algorithm is basically clever another kind of reasoning is the
clever another kind of reasoning is the desirable algorithm because have much
理想的算法，因为它比线性化具有更高的精度
desirable algorithm because have much higher accuracy than the linearization
higher accuracy than the linearization that we discussed before okay and the
我们之前讨论过的，反对意见是您已经对此进行了优化
that we discussed before okay and the objection is you have optimized this
objection is you have optimized this various points don't may be the function
各个点可能不是函数，您知道它非常好
various points don't may be the function and you know it's very nice
and you know it's very nice extermination to program you don't have
无需编程就可以消灭它，所以您没有给他们任何东西
extermination to program you don't have to program so you didn't give them any
to program so you didn't give them any hormones to program this right but
激素来编程这项权利，但也许你应该给他们
hormones to program this right but things maybe you should give them
things maybe you should give them something worth a download maybe one of
值得下载的东西，可能是其中一种算法，还有一部
something worth a download maybe one of the algorithms and the play with a
the algorithms and the play with a tortoise you can plot to see how the
您可以绘图的乌龟，看看平托如何
tortoise you can plot to see how the Pinto
Pinto looks like you know how this malting
看起来您知道这种麦芽分配的样子，并且和
looks like you know how this malting distribution looks like and and and the
distribution looks like and and and the like just to finish the 125 right
就像刚刚完成第125个任务一样显然，这个星云听起来很小一部分
like just to finish the 125 right obviously this nebula sound a small part
obviously this nebula sound a small part of this whole area of data stimulation
整个数据刺激区域的正确性，因此提示可以处理动态数据
of this whole area of data stimulation right so cue work with dynamical data
right so cue work with dynamical data you need to know all of the specifics up
您需要知道每个细节上下的所有细节，因为
you need to know all of the specifics up and down every single detail because
and down every single detail because playing with data in time requires that
及时处理数据需要您进行预测，然后做一些小事情
playing with data in time requires that you do prediction you do small things of
you do prediction you do small things of filtering all right all of the above
过滤以上所有内容，好了，新功能很多
filtering all right all of the above okay there are lots of power of new
okay there are lots of power of new books that are coming out on data
关于数据刺激的书籍装扮得有点破烂
books that are coming out on data stimulation dressed up with a little bit
stimulation dressed up with a little bit of mathematics they don't contain
他们不包含任何新东西，因为这个想法有
of mathematics they don't contain anything new because this ideas have
anything new because this ideas have been out there for 20 years
在那里呆了20年了，但是想要对的人我是说
been out there for 20 years okay but people who want right I mean if
okay but people who want right I mean if you want to write a book you know you
你想写一本书，你知道你可以在卡尔曼滤波上做一些事情六
you want to write a book you know you can do something on Kalman filtering six
can do something on Kalman filtering six months okay
几个月就可以了，然后有人可以读懂
months okay and then someone can read it you know
and then someone can read it you know how many also to the three hours okay
到三个小时还好几个，而且总有东西要做
how many also to the three hours okay and and always there's something to make
and and always there's something to make it different
没关系，但最后您的公式是
it different okay but in the end you the formulas are
okay but in the end you the formulas are in the books already in papers and you
在已经有论文的书中，您可以阅读，所以在星期四，
in the books already in papers and you can read them and so on Thursday we're
can read them and so on Thursday we're going to change subject and move the
将要改变主题并将身体移至变分近似方法
going to change subject and move the body to variational approximate method
body to variational approximate method okay and where we need to spend at least
好的，我们需要花至少三四堂课讨论聚酯
okay and where we need to spend at least three or four lectures discuss polyester
three or four lectures discuss polyester on that okay
没关系，我要发表很多东西
on that okay a lot of stuff to read I'm going to post
a lot of stuff to read I'm going to post this lectures today so you guys can take
今天的讲座，所以你们可以看看，然后从那里拿走
this lectures today so you guys can take a look and and take it from there all
a look and and take it from there all right
正确的